<?xml version="1.0"?>
<gameList>
	<game>
		<path>./Legend of Zelda, The - Link's Awakening DX.gbc</path>
		<name>Legend of Zelda, The - Link's Awakening DX</name>
		<playcount>3</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20201103T113640</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Wario Land II.gbc</path>
		<name>Wario Land II</name>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20201104T004646</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Legend of Zelda, The - Oracle of Ages.gbc</path>
		<name>Legend of Zelda, The - Oracle of Ages</name>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20201104T014522</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Bomberman Max - Blue Champion.gbc</path>
		<name>Bomberman Max: Blue Champion</name>
		<desc>In Bomberman Max, your task is to jump through five zones with a dozen levels each. At the beginning of the round, you're given your quota to meet -- in some levels, you'll have to destroy all the enemies. In another, wipe out all the blocks in the land. In another, rescue the level's Charabomb. And in others, simply make your way to the target square in the set amount of time. But it won't be easy, since many enemies just don't stay still for you to walk up and plant a bomb next to them. It's all in the strategy of bomb-placement. Plus, once a level's complete, you'll have to pick the proper exit that appears. Released in two versions, Blue and Red.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gbc/Bomberman Max - Blue Champion-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20000514T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hudson Entertainment, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Vatical Entertainment LLC</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Bomberman Max - Red Challenger.gbc</path>
		<name>Bomberman Max: Red Challenger</name>
		<desc>n Bomberman Max, your task is to jump through five zones with a dozen levels each. At the beginning of the round, you're given your quota to meet -- in some levels, you'll have to destroy all the enemies. In another, wipe out all the blocks in the land. In another, rescue the level's Charabomb. And in others, simply make your way to the target square in the set amount of time. But it won't be easy, since many enemies just don't stay still for you to walk up and plant a bomb next to them. It's all in the strategy of bomb-placement. Plus, once a level's complete, you'll have to pick the proper exit that appears. Released in two versions, Blue and Red.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gbc/Bomberman Max - Red Challenger-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20000514T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hudson Entertainment, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Vatical Entertainment LLC</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Bomberman Quest.gbc</path>
		<name>Bomberman Quest</name>
		<desc>Bomberman is on his way home when the engines on his ship are stolen. As a result, he must make an emergency landing on a strange planet. However, Bomberman is not traveling alone he's got all of the monsters he has captured on his adventures with him. After a rough crash landing, the monsters escaped. You must help Bomberman recapture the monsters and find his engines in order to return home. You'll travel to four different regions of the planet collecting bombs, finding items, and getting hints for how to proceed on your adventure. Along with the main quest a Two-Player mode is also included, in which you try to trap your opponent by setting bombs; the first person to be victimized by a bomb loses.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gbc/Bomberman Quest-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19991101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Eleven</developer>
		<publisher>Electro-Brain</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Bugs Bunny - Crazy Castle 4.gbc</path>
		<name>Bugs Bunny In Crazy Castle 3</name>
		<desc>Bugs Bunny returns to crazy puzzle or action gaming on Game boy Color. Once again you play as the legendary Bugs Bunny as he explores the mysterious Crazy Castle in search of the mother lode of carrots. The castle has all-new rooms with all-new puzzles, so prepare yourself for even more hare-brained action than the last time around. The Crazy Castle is chock-full of hazards and traps that will end your merry little jaunt in a hurry, so keep a sharp eye out. In order to test your reflexes as well as your wits, several Warner Bros. cartoon characters have returned to make Bugs's life that much more difficult! Fight off Sylvester, Daffy Duck, Yosemite Sam, Elmer Fudd, Tweety Bird, and the Tazmanian Devil with one of your weapons, or just turn tail and run as fast as you can. Naturally, the game comes complete with a password function so you can explore the floors at your leisure once you've cleared them.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gbc/Bugs Bunny - Crazy Castle 4-image.png</image>
		<releasedate>19990101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Kemco</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Bust-A-Move 4.gbc</path>
		<name>Bust-A-Move 4</name>
		<desc>You'll be Forever Bursting Bubbles! Bust-A-Move-4 is bursting onto the scene with more advanced gameplay, and tons of new features. It's a challenge for the whole family!

* Bury opponents with the devastating new Chain Reactions.
* Keep the bubbles in balance with the new Pulley Mechanism.
* Rank yourself with the comprehensive Ranking System.
* Save custom puzzles to Memory Cards with Edit Mode.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gbc/Bust-A-Move 4-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19990506T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Crawfish Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Acclaim Entertainment, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Bust-A-Move Millennium.gbc</path>
		<name>Bust-A-Move Millennium</name>
		<desc>BUST-A-MOVE MILENNIUM EDITION on Game Boy Color brings a bevy of often-requested new features to this classic puzzler. Bubbles of different colors descend from the top of the screen in clumps. Using your blaster that fires colored bubbles of your own, you must attempt to clear the screen as best as you can. BUST-A-MOVE MILENNIUM EDITION offers five unique modes of play. In the returning Puzzle mode, you'll play through a huge number of new stages of bubble-busting action that require careful planning and fast reflexes. Challenge mode also returns to test your BUST-A-MOVE skills. In the brand new Story mode, you'll take on a series of increasingly difficult computer opponents in a battle to the finish. Also new is a mode that allows you to play as long as you can last. Of course, the biggest and best addition to BUST-A-MOVE MILENNIUM EDITION is the two-player link cable Versus mode. Now you can grab a friend and show off your BUST-A-MOVE skills! You get all of this plus enhanced graphics and other new options.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gbc/Bust-A-Move Millennium-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20001011T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Taito Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>Acclaim Entertainment, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Classic Bubble Bobble.gbc</path>
		<name>Classic Bubble Bobble</name>
		<desc>The addictive arcade classic comes to Game Boy Color in CLASSIC BUBBLE BOBBLE. Bob has fallen sick, and it's up to Bub to traverse a strange world to find the cure. Each of the game's 100+ levels is filled to the brim with enemies, but luckily you've got a trusty weapon at your disposal your bubble shot that you use to trap the monsters! Once trapped in their soapy prison, you can pop them just by touching the bubble. Once you clear out all the enemies in a stage, it's time to float over to the next one. Collect power-ups to increase your speed, freeze your enemies, or even shoot special bubbles that fire off dazzling electricity attacks. You'll do battle against a variety of bizarre and sometimes very large enemies as you work to cure Bob's illness. CLASSIC BUBBLE BOBBLE features new graphics, including all-new backgrounds so you're bound to have a new experience every time you play.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gbc/Classic Bubble Bobble-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19990101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Dreams</developer>
		<publisher>Metro3D, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Cubix - Robots for Everyone - Race 'n Robots.gbc</path>
		<name>Cubix: Robots For Everyone - Race 'N Robots</name>
		<desc>Robots in everyday life? Believe it, folks. That's the reality of the cool cartoon series, CUBIX: Robots for Everyone. The story follows the adventures of Connor a human boy and his robot, Cubix, through Bubble Town. Attempting to repair damaged robots and ward off evil beings, the pair encounters a whole cast of wacky characters every week. The game puts its emphasis on the racing aspects of the series, sending you to Bubble Town's racing championship series. Your arch-nemesis, Dr. K, has a converted racer named Kolossal in the competition, and your goal is to earn the right to defeat it. Choose to race as any of your favorite series characters, including Hop2ix, Brutix, Don-Don, Diagnostix, and Cubix. You'll be able to customize your racers to fit your liking, using elements like Grav-grip, Zero G, and other series-based power-ups to defy gravity and reach top speeds. Full of cool options game modes, and colorful graphics, Race N Robots is not to be missed.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gbc/Cubix - Robots for Everyone - Race 'n Robots-image.png</image>
		<releasedate>20011113T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Blitz Games</developer>
		<publisher>3DO</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Donkey Kong Country.gbc</path>
		<name>Donkey Kong Country</name>
		<desc>The best-selling Super NES game of all time is back! Remember blasting through levels in barrels and taking wild mine cart rides? All the jammin' jungle hi-jinks are back, along with DK's animal friends Rambi the Rhino, Squawks the Parrot, Enguarde the Swordfish and more! In addition to all the original levels, you get the chest-pounding fun of new bonus levels and 2-player games.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gbc/Donkey Kong Country-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20001123T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rare, Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dragon Warrior I &amp; II.gbc</path>
		<name>Dragon Warrior I &amp; II</name>
		<desc>Step back into the wondrous land of Alefgard and defeat the evil DracoLord in the standard-setting Gragon Warrior I. Continue your amazing adventure and banish the foul Hargon in Dragon Warrior II. With tons of monsters to fight, treasures to find and mysteries to explore, you may never want to turn off your Game Boy Color again!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gbc/Dragon Warrior I &amp; II-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20000927T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tose Co., Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Enix Corporation</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dragon Warrior III.gbc</path>
		<name>Dragon Warrior III</name>
		<desc>Your father, the brave Ortega, is dead. He set off to destroy the Demon Lord Baramos but fell in glorious battle. Unless stopped, Baramos will unleash a torrent of evil that will destroy the world. You must stop Baramos and discover the legend of Dragon Warrior! Your journey starts on Aliahan. Only you decide where it ends...</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gbc/Dragon Warrior III-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20010716T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tose Co., Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Enix Corporation</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dragon Warrior Monsters.gbc</path>
		<name>Dragon Warrior Monsters</name>
		<desc>In Dragon Warrior Monsters, enter Terry’s Wonderland, a magical place of kings, monsters and magic spells.  Make monsters your allies to fight through the dangers that lie ahead in the long quest.  Find your kidnapped sister and become the most powerful monster master in the world!

Each monster has unique special skills to use in battle.  Train and treat them well, and you’ll be victorious!  Over 40,000 different combinations - can you breed the rarest and most powerful monsters?

* Over 200 cute &amp; cool monsters to collect, tame, and train.
* Breed your trained monsters to make more powerful monsters, each receiving special skills from their parent monsters.
* Play solo, or use the Game Link cable to link to Game Boy game systems and battle and breed with your friends’ monsters.
* A spin off of Japan’s best selling RPG game, Enix’s Dragon Quest.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gbc/Dragon Warrior Monsters-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20000127T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Enix, Tose</developer>
		<publisher>Eidos Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dragon Warrior Monsters 2 - Cobi's Journey.gbc</path>
		<name>Dragon Warrior Monsters 2: Cobi's Journey</name>
		<desc>When Cobi and Tara's family of monster farmers moves out to the island of GreatLog, it quickly becomes apparent that all is not well in their new homeland. The island's prince, Kameha, and his ill-willed accomplice, Warubou, quickly confront the brother-and-sister team. Now, the dastardly pair has embarked on a plot to sink the entire island, and you'll have to train an army of Dragon Warrior Monsters to help stop the evil crime. This installment casts you as the brother, Cobi challenging you to find hidden keys and prepare all of your monsters for battle. There are more than 300 battling beasts in all, which means that you'll have your work cut out for you if you hope to effectively utilize your troops. As you wander through the land, you'll encounter different monsters, which you can persuade to join your team by offering up treats. You can also trade beings with other players who own the game or have a copy of DRAGON WARRIOR MONSTERS 2: Tara's Adventure (the parallel release, which follows the story of Cobi's sister).</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gbc/Dragon Warrior Monsters 2 - Cobi's Journey-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20010915T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tose Co., Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Enix Corporation</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dragon Warrior Monsters 2 - Tara's Adventure.gbc</path>
		<name>Dragon Warrior Monsters 2: Tara's Adventure</name>
		<desc>The wildly successful DRAGON WARRIOR MONSTERS returns to handheld form with parallel releases DRAGON WARRIOR MONSTERS 2: Tara's Adventure and DRAGON WARRIOR MONSTERS 2: Cobi's Journey. This installment focuses on the efforts of the sister, Tara, as she tries to end an evil plot to stop her new homeland from sinking. Prince Kameha and his ill-willed accomplice, Warubou, are responsible for the mischief, and you've got to help Tara collect and train more than 300 fighting monsters in order to reverse the deadly plan. Make your way through the countryside, collecting valuable keys and recruiting monsters to help battle evil. Each beast you encounter will need to be persuaded to help you out, which you can do by offering up various forms of foods and treats. With better graphics than most of its competition, the game even lets you trade monsters with other players who own either installment of the addicting DRAGON MONSTER WARRIORS 2 collection.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gbc/Dragon Warrior Monsters 2 - Tara's Adventure-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20010915T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tose Co., Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Enix Corporation</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dragon's Lair.gbc</path>
		<name>Dragon's Lair</name>
		<desc>Dirk the Daring is back! Control the fate of Dirk the Daring in the long-awaited return of Dragon's Lair, now for Game Boy Color. The fair princess, Daphne has been seized by the evil dragon, Singe and only Dirk the Daring can rescue her from his clutches. On your quest, you must fight your way through the castle of the dark wizard who has enchanted it with treacherous monsters, traps and other obstacles. Lead on brave adventurer!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gbc/Dragon's Lair-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20010115T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Digital Eclipse Software, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Earthworm Jim - Menace 2 the Galaxy.gbc</path>
		<name>Earthworm Jim: Menace 2 the Galaxy</name>
		<desc>Earthworm Jim is back, and he's brought a ton of mayhem and destruction with him! EARTHWORM JIM: Menace 2 the Galaxy is the second Game Boy Color adventure for everyone's favorite worm-turned-superhero. Playing as Jim in this one-player action game, you must blast your way through 12 bizarre stages packed with enemies and other hazards. To aid you in your endeavor, you'll be able to pick up and use four different weapons to toast your foes. The typical wry humor present in the EARTHWORM JIM series is here as well, resulting in some crazy situations for you to jump, shoot, and fly your way through. Although EARTHWORM JIM: Menace 2 the Galaxy is compatible with all Game Boy systems, it includes a special exclusive level when played on Game Boy Color.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gbc/Earthworm Jim - Menace 2 the Galaxy-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19991110T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>David A. Palmer Productions</developer>
		<publisher>Crave Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Frogger.gbc</path>
		<name>Frogger</name>
		<desc>It's tough to be a frog! Life isn't all lazy days and lily pads--it abounds with dangers. Can you help Frogger survive some perils and spring him home to safety? First hop your frogs across a busy highway. Then cross a raging river to reach the safety of home. But your frogs will have to leap away from one danger after another before they're safe. Watch out for the tricky diving turtles...jump away from the frog-eating snakes...hop from the jaws of the hungry alligators!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gbc/Frogger-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19981231T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Morning Star Multimedia</developer>
		<publisher>Majesco Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Frogger 2.gbc</path>
		<name>Frogger 2: Swampy's Revenge</name>
		<desc>It's fast and furious action from start to finish for Frogger and his new friend, Lillie Frog. Help them save the Frog Babies from Swampy the crocodile.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gbc/Frogger 2-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20000923T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Morning Star Multimedia</developer>
		<publisher>Hasbro Interactive, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ghosts'n Goblins.gbc</path>
		<name>Ghosts 'n Goblins</name>
		<desc>Capcom's arcade-turn-console action platformer Ghosts 'N Goblins is a true 2D classic. The game, which stars Sir Arthur, a knight on a mission to rescue Princess Guinevere, travels players through six huge 2D scrolling levels rained with obstacles, enemies and other infuriating hazards. It was all too easy to meet one's doom at the near end of a stage as the difficulty level is unforgiving and have to start all over, but because of the clever coin-munching design and atmospheric presentation, the drag to keep playing never loosened. It's still regarded as one of the greats. The GBC version, released in 2000, is a direct port of the NES game.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gbc/Ghosts'n Goblins-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20000101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Digital Eclipse Software, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Grand Theft Auto.gbc</path>
		<name>Grand Theft Auto</name>
		<desc>Experience for yourself every classic car chase ever seen. Race at breakneck speed through an immense, living city out-running and out-witting rival gang members, mercenaries, hired killers and an entire police force.

Drive dozens of varied vehicles around three of America's toughest cities. Only the best will be able to tame the fastest cars. Only the smartest will know all the short-cuts and the whereabouts of the hottest wheels. Only the toughest will be able to take on the world and finish the job like a professional...</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gbc/Grand Theft Auto-image.png</image>
		<releasedate>19991101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tarantula Studios</developer>
		<publisher>Rockstar Games</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Hamtaro - Ham-Hams Unite!.gbc</path>
		<name>Hamtaro: Ham-Hams Unite!</name>
		<desc>Hamtaro: Ham-Hams Unite! is a Role-Playing game, developed by Pax Softonica and published by Nintendo, which was released in 2001.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gbc/Hamtaro - Ham-Hams Unite!-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20021028T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Pax Softnica</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets.gbc</path>
		<name>Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets</name>
		<desc>Ignoring Dobbya the house-elf's grave warning that disaster will strike if he returns to Hogwarts, Harry embarks on his second year to find Dobby's predictions coming true! Harry soon finds himself entangled in a dark plot against his "Mudblood" classmates, as students keep turning up petrified! Could Draco Malfoya be to blame, or is something even more malevolent at work? With the help of returning friends Hermione, Ron, Hagrida and Hedwiga, players attend new classes to learn second-year spells that will aid them in a quest to uncover the true identity of the "Heir of Slytherin".</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gbc/Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20021101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Griptonite Games</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Harry Potter and the Sorcerer's Stone.gbc</path>
		<name>Harry Potter and the Sorcerer's Stone</name>
		<desc>Unlike other game versions of the first Harry Potter book, the Game Boy Color rendition of Harry Potter and the Sorcerer's Stone is a traditional roleplaying game, complete with NPCs to talk to and random beastie battles to challenge you. The game begins with the receipt of an acceptance letter into Hogwarts School of Witchcraft and Wizardry. From there, you (as Harry Potter, of course) will go shopping for your school supplies, catch the train on the 9 3/4 platform, take a boat ride, and finally arrive at your new home.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gbc/Harry Potter and the Sorcerer's Stone-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20011115T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>KnowWonder</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Harvest Moon.gbc</path>
		<name>Harvest Moon 2 GBC</name>
		<desc>Rebuild the farm of your grandfather and start raising cows, chickens and sheep. Keep them happy and they’ll make you rich! Discover the fantastic Harvest Moon world with cool friends ready to help you succeed in your mission.

- The awaited Harvest Moon sequel for GBC with even more fun!
- Choice of playing a boy or girl farmer
- Hours and hours of gameplay
- Hidden arcade games include Mole Bash and Cherry Cup Horse Race
- Special Game Link cable options allow trading between Harvest Moon 2 and Legend of the River King 2</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gbc/Harvest Moon-image.png</image>
		<releasedate>20001107T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Natsume</developer>
		<publisher>Natsume</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Harvest Moon 2.gbc</path>
		<name>Harvest Moon 2 GBC</name>
		<desc>Rebuild the farm of your grandfather and start raising cows, chickens and sheep. Keep them happy and they’ll make you rich! Discover the fantastic Harvest Moon world with cool friends ready to help you succeed in your mission.

- The awaited Harvest Moon sequel for GBC with even more fun!
- Choice of playing a boy or girl farmer
- Hours and hours of gameplay
- Hidden arcade games include Mole Bash and Cherry Cup Horse Race
- Special Game Link cable options allow trading between Harvest Moon 2 and Legend of the River King 2</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gbc/Harvest Moon 2-image.png</image>
		<releasedate>20001107T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Natsume</developer>
		<publisher>Natsume</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Harvest Moon 3.gbc</path>
		<name>Harvest Moon 3 GBC</name>
		<desc>The third entry in the down-home series of RPGs boasts a bevy of new options and features. You can play as a male or female farmer, get married, play with new pets and enjoy new minigames.

Essentially a farming role-playing game, Harvest Moon 3 requires you to clear a patch of land, till the soil, plant seeds and tend the new shoots. Take a twice-weekly ferry to the mainland (the island locale is new to this game) to purchase animals and other supplies.

Despite -- or perhaps because of -- the lack of swordplay, magic spells and other traditional RPG fare, the Harvest Moon series exerts its own unique charm that has won over thousands of would-be farmers worldwide.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gbc/Harvest Moon 3-image.png</image>
		<releasedate>20011114T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Natsume</developer>
		<publisher>Natsume</publisher>
		<genre>Construction and Management Simulation, Life Simulation</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Kirby - Tilt 'n' Tumble.gbc</path>
		<name>Koro Koro Kirby</name>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gbc/Kirby - Tilt 'n' Tumble-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20000823T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Puzzle</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Legend of Zelda - Link's Awakening DX.gbc</path>
		<name>Legend of Zelda - Link's Awakening DX</name>
		<playcount>2</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20210219T063727</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Legend of Zelda - Oracle of Ages.gbc</path>
		<name>Legend Of Zelda - Oracle Of Ages, The</name>
		<desc>Using the legendary power of the Triforce, Link travels to a distant land known as Labrynna where Veran, the Sorceress of Shadows, has developed a scheme to alter Labrynna's past. Through trickery and deceit, Veran harnesses the power of Nayru, the Oracle of Ages, and travels 400 years into the past. Before the Sorceress of Shadows can complete her dark mission, Link must use the Harp of Ages to save the day.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gbc/Legend of Zelda - Oracle of Ages-image.png</image>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20010513T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Flagship</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mega Man Xtreme.gbc</path>
		<name>Mega Man Xtreme</name>
		<desc>The future world is in turmoil. The peace keeping mother computer has been hacked and a virus runs rampant throughout the world. Only Mega Man X has the ability to traverse eight dangerous levels in cyberspace, battle huge bosses along the way and restore the mother computer to its normal state. When the going gets too intence, Mega Man X's pal, Zero can be summoned to help him out of the most dangerous situations. It's an X-treme situation that only Mega Man X can resolve!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gbc/Mega Man Xtreme-image.png</image>
		<releasedate>20010111T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mega Man Xtreme 2.gbc</path>
		<name>Mega Man Xtreme 2</name>
		<desc>Something mysterious is going on at the reploid research island. The reploids have ceased functionality... their data strangely erased. Now the investigation team encounters "irregular" reploids infected with a strange new DNA chip. This strange DNA chip, known as "DNA Soul", replaces useful data with a devastating Sigma virus and places all reploids in imminent danger. Now, it's up to Mega Man X and his comrade, Zero, to get to the damaged island and find out who is behind the DNA Soul virus.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gbc/Mega Man Xtreme 2-image.png</image>
		<releasedate>20011030T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Metal Gear Solid.gbc</path>
		<name>Metal Gear Solid</name>
		<desc>Early 21st Century. An incident that rocks the US government takes place. The classified weapon and nuclear-launching bipedal tank Metal Gear has fallen into the hands of terrorists. Seven years after the fiasco at Outer Heaven involving the original Metal Gear, the US government calls in Solid Snake to neutralize the terrorist threat.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gbc/Metal Gear Solid-image.png</image>
		<releasedate>20000505T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Stealth</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Monster Rancher Battle Card.gbc</path>
		<name>Monster Rancher Battle Card GB</name>
		<desc>Before the world's continents broke up into pieces, a huge disaster hit the world. People prayed to God for help, and God created new life forms. However, new life forms brought new troubles, so God became exasperated and sealed them in "disc stones". Many years have passed since then and God entrusted the humans with the secret of "disc stones". Today people still continue searching for these missing "disc stones" to unlock the lifeforms within. In the anime, the monsters were created by scientists.
It is said that the "disc stones" are almost impossible to find among the ancient ruins. It is said that one monster is trapped inside each one. One day a group of workers excavating the ancient ruins happened to dig up one of these mythical disc stones. The worker who first discovered a disc stone took the disc to the Monsters' Temple. There the priests, using the ancient methods, unlocked the monster inside the disc stone. In a place where ranchers and monsters coexisted peacefully, the battle of the monsters began. As time passed these monster battles became extremely popular, and monster breeding became the standard pastime of the land. Eventually disc stones were found around the entire world. Now ranchers across the globe come together and enter unto battle.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gbc/Monster Rancher Battle Card-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20000401T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Graphic Research Co., Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Tecmo</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Monster Rancher Explorer.gbc</path>
		<name>Monster Rancher Explorer</name>
		<desc>The MONSTER RANCHER franchise returns with this thoroughly entertaining adventure for handheld gamers. Help the well-meaning Cox fight through 60 enormous, puzzle-filled levels, fending off certain monsters while allying yourself with others. Each level requires you to find a hidden key in order to advance to the next stage, a task that becomes increasingly difficult as things progress. Luckily, you're not going at it alone. You can unlock such friendly beasts as Gali, Hare, Mocchi, Suezo, and Tiger in order to help you fend off all enemies. Each of the friendly monsters serves as a power-up of sorts, increasing your overall speed, granting you temporary invincibility, and more. Fans of the series know just how fun collecting and utilizing monsters can be, and the premise is at its absolute best in this GBA installment. Cool, anime-style graphics abound throughout the massive gaming experience, which allows you to play alone or square off against a fellow Rancher.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gbc/Monster Rancher Explorer-image.png</image>
		<releasedate>20001001T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Graphic Research Co., Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Tecmo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mortal Kombat 4.gbc</path>
		<name>Mortal Kombat 4</name>
		<desc>Two fighters enter the arena; the winner will move on in the tournament, the other will be dead. This tournament for control of Earth has been going on for centuries and continues in MORTAL KOMBAT 4. Choose from eight different characters: Fujin, Liu Kang, Sub Zero, Tanya, Quan Chi, Raiden, Reiko, Shinnok, Scorpion, and a few hidden characters as well. Each character has unique moves, combinations, and fatalities, and when you properly execute a fatality, a short animated reenactment plays. Throughout the game, there are special Kombat Kodes that are exclusive to the Game Boy Color, and you'll also get quite a bit of in-game speech. If you think you are the strongest fighter, prove it with MORTAL KOMBAT 4.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gbc/Mortal Kombat 4-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19981201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Digital Eclipse Software, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Midway Games</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mr. Driller.gbc</path>
		<name>Mr. Driller</name>
		<desc>Mr Driller is a real-time puzzle game that relies solely on quick-thinking and a bit of planning. Gameplay is a combination of Tetris and Boulder Dash: You have to drill down through multi-colored blocks to reach the bottom while avoiding the consequences of reckless drilling (blocks may fall on you and crush you).</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gbc/Mr. Driller-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19990317T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ms. Pac-Man - Special Color Edition.gbc</path>
		<name>Ms. Pac-Man: Special Color Edition</name>
		<desc>All of the action and fun of the first feminist arcade game can be put in the palm of your hand with MS. PAC-MAN: Special Color Edition. You take control of the yellow disk adorned with lipstick and a pink bow, better known as the lovely Ms. Pac-Man. The goal is to guide her around the maze and eat all of the dots, avoiding the four ghosts that chase you. There are power pellets located in each corner of the maze which, when eaten, turn the ghosts blue. Once this happens, the ghosts can be eaten. Occasionally, fruit will float into the maze, which can be munched for extra points. If your friends want to play along, there is an alternating Two-Player mode. As an additional bonus, a complete version of SUPER PAC-MAN is included on the cartridge. Play as the first female arcade hero in MS. PAC-MAN: Special Color Edition.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gbc/Ms. Pac-Man - Special Color Edition-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19991102T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Nicktoons Racing.gbc</path>
		<name>NickToons Racing</name>
		<desc>Characters from your favorite Nicktoons are motorin' for victory in this Game Boy Color racer! Get on the Rugrats track... watch out for those Angry Beavers ... steer clear of SpongeBob SquarePants. Race on multiple tracks based on your favorite Nicktoons - Tommy, SpongeBob SquarePants, Eliza, The Angry Beavers, CatDog and Arnold. Whether you play alone or against a friend, it looks like a wild ride ahead!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gbc/Nicktoons Racing-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20001207T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Pipe Dream Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Majesco Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pitfall - Beyond the Jungle.gbc</path>
		<name>Pitfall: Beyond the Jungle</name>
		<desc>An evil force known as Scourge is manipulating the Red Lucense in order to take over the jungle. Now it is up to Pitfall Harry Jr. to use the Blue Lucense to restore peace to the land. You control Harry as he battles through 15 levels that span jungles, volcanoes, prisons, and caverns. Each world has unique variations; for example, you have to swing from vines in the jungle stages, while using a pickaxe to battle scorpions and other monsters. For some additional help, Harry has quick reflexes to allow him to dodge bullets and jump over some of the bad guys. In addition to Harry's innate skills, there are power-ups scattered throughout the levels including extra lives, gold bars, crystals, and extra health. Help Harry restore peace to the jungle in PITFALL: Beyond the Jungle.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gbc/Pitfall - Beyond the Jungle-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19981201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>David A. Palmer Productions</developer>
		<publisher>Crave Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pokemon - Crystal Version.gbc</path>
		<name>Pokémon Crystal Version</name>
		<desc>Pocket Monster mania continues with Nintendo's release of Pokémon Crystal for the Game Boy Color. Much as 1999's Pokémon Yellow offered gentle enhancements to the basic story and gameplay of the original Pokémon Red and Pokémon Blue games, Pokémon Crystal is based on the second-wave Pokémon Gold and Pokémon Silver releases.

Though it follows the same story told in the Gold and Silver versions, Pokémon Crystal has some new options and special features. For the first time, gamers have the choice to play as a female trainer in this version. Also, just as Pokémon Yellow included a special Pikachu, trainers are aided by an unusual Suicune in this release. Pokémon Crystal is designed to offer a complete Pokémon experience for those new to the ubiquitous phenomenon and additional challenges for seasoned trainers who simply have to catch 'em all.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gbc/Pokemon - Crystal Version-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20001214T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Game Freak</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure, Role-Playing</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pokemon - Gold Version.gbc</path>
		<name>Pokémon Gold Version</name>
		<desc>Enter a whole new world, with new Pokémon to capture, train and battle! Meet Professor Elm and get the all-new Poké Gear, including map, radio, cell phone and clock. Set the clock then watch as day turns to night and events take place in real time—and be sure to keep an eye out for Pokémon that come out only at night!

• Dozens of never-before-seen Pokémon! Find new evolutions for some familiar Pokémon and discover whole new species. Your Pokédex will even reveal genders of some Pokémon.
• A whole new world! Explore Johto, where there are new gym leaders to beat and eight new badges to earn.
• Two new types! Introducing Dark and Steel-type Pokémon.
• Trade with Silver, Red, Blue, and Yellow versions to catch ‘em all!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gbc/Pokemon - Gold Version-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19991121T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Game Freak</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure, Role-Playing</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pokemon - Silver Version.gbc</path>
		<name>Pokémon Silver Version</name>
		<desc>Enter a whole new world, with new Pokémon to capture, train and battle!  Meet Professor Elm and get the all-new Poké Gear, including map, radio, cell phone and clock.  Set the clock then watch as day turns to night and events take place in real time—and be sure to keep an eye out for Pokémon that come out only at night!

• Dozens of never-before-seen Pokémon!  Find new evolutions for some familiar Pokémon and discover whole new species.  Your Pokédex will even reveal genders of some Pokémon.
• A whole new world!  Explore Johto, where there are new gym leaders to beat and eight new badges to earn.
• Two new types!  Introducing Dark and Steel-type Pokémon.
• Trade with Gold, Red, Blue, and Yellow versions to catch ‘em all!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gbc/Pokemon - Silver Version-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19991121T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Game Freak</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure, Role-Playing</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pokemon Pinball.gbc</path>
		<name>Pokémon Pinball</name>
		<desc>There are two tables in the game, red and blue. Each table has its own details and gameplay elements.

Each table has different "locations" that you play, which determine which Pokémon are available for capture. A subset of available locations are displayed slot-machine style in the beginning of a game, and pressing A will select your starting location and launch the first ball into play. After that, each table has its own mechanism for advancing to the next location, including the locations not available at the start of the game.

"Catch Mode," when activated, starts a 2 minute window of opportunity where you can attempt to capture a Pokémon. Once you activate "catch mode," you must hit the pop bumpers 6 times. Each hit unlocks 1/6 of an image of the Pokémon currently up for capture. Once the image is complete, the Pokémon appears on the table, where it must be hit 4 times with the ball to capture it.

"Evolution Mode," when activated, starts a 2 minute window of opportunity where you select a captured Pokémon (from the current game in progress only) and attempt to evolve it into another form. This is the only way to add the evolved form to your Pokédex. Once you select a Pokémon, you must hit targets on the playfield. There are up to 6 targets, but only 3 of them have items in them you need to evolve a Pokémon. The others create a time-wasting sequence before you can hit targets again. If you hit a target with an item, the item appears on the playfield and must be collected with the ball. Once you've collected 3 items, the hole in the center of the board opens up. Sinking the ball in the hole successfully evolves the Pokémon.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gbc/Pokemon Pinball-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19990628T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Jupiter Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle, Shooter</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pokemon Trading Card Game.gbc</path>
		<name>Pokémon Trading Card Game</name>
		<desc>Your goal in life is to become a Pokemon Card Master. In order to do that, you must pick a deck from three starter packs of cards based on Charmander, Squirtle, and Bulbasaur and travel to the eight card clubs and defeat their leaders. Along the way, you will challenge many players to collect new cards and the helpful Professor Mason will aid you by giving you cards as well. While becoming a card master is a laudable accomplishment, the real goal of the game is to collect all of the cards over 200 in all. If you want to collect all of the cards, you must play human opponents in the Pop mode to get a chance to earn rare cards. All of the complexity of the real-world game has been captured here. Play Pokemon Trading Card Game and become a Pokemon Card Master.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gbc/Pokemon Trading Card Game-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20000410T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Power Quest.gbc</path>
		<name>Power Quest</name>
		<desc>The gameplay of Power Quest is a mixture of two genres: RPG and fighting game similar to Hissatsu Doujou Yaburi, Tenkaichi Bushi Keru Naguru and Metal &amp; Lace: Battle of the Robo Babes. You venture around the town in which you live on an overworld map where you can go to different locations. Once you arrive at a location, a character appears on the screen with some dialogue. More often than not this dialog involves the character challenging you to a fight. After you are challenged by a character, the game switches to a one-on-one fighting game engine. This is the RPG's battle system which differs from the usual turn-based battle engine's of the genre.
You can buy new parts for your Model which is how you gain experience throughout the game. You progress through the game by challenging a certain amount of people before the next event is triggered. Then special events pop up throughout the game after this number is met which usually involve a tournament or beating some strong boss-type character.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gbc/Power Quest-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19991201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Japan System Supply</developer>
		<publisher>SUNSOFT</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing, Fighting</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Rampage - World Tour.gbc</path>
		<name>Rampage: World Tour</name>
		<desc>Purebred destruction is the name of the game in RAMPAGE WORLD TOUR. Choose one of three different monsters (each a gargantuan tower of rage), and then join your counterparts as you wreak holy terror on city after city. You'll stomp buildings, crush cars, and even take down innocent pedestrians in your strides to do as much damage as possible. Parents can rest assured: although the game's focus is on tearing apart the scenery, there's little of the blood and gore that pervades many video games these days. There are more than 130 stages to romp through in this tribute to silver screen terrors, and each level presents all-new challenges and more difficult gameplay. If you're familiar with the RAMPAGE series, you'll love the inclusion of three new monsters to take the place of the familiar faces from the original game. The play is faithful to previous titles in the RAMPAGE series, but improved graphics and controls make for the most exhilarating entry to date. Devastation has never been so fun!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gbc/Rampage - World Tour-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19981201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Digital Eclipse Software, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Rampage 2 - Universal Tour.gbc</path>
		<name>Rampage 2: Universal Tour</name>
		<desc>Giant monsters are attacking the world's cities and you just happen to be one of the monsters. You can choose from six different beasts, including a gorilla, wolf, rat, lizard, lobster, and rhino. Each character has unique strengths and weaknesses, plus a unique special attack. Earn points by demolishing all of the buildings, downing helicopters, destroying tanks, and eating the helpless citizens. When you are hit by the human defenses, you lose power from your life meter. As luck would have it, health power-ups are located in each level, including a special food for each character that boosts their abilities. There are 100 cities to destroy, along with a Two-Player option that allows a friend to join the destructive action. Send the human race back to the Stone Age with RAMPAGE 2: Universal Tour.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gbc/Rampage 2 - Universal Tour-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19991101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Digital Eclipse Software, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Midway Games</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Rayman.gbc</path>
		<name>Rayman</name>
		<desc>Rayman is side-scrolling platformer starring the titular Rayman, a big-nosed chap with no arms or legs. Rayman can jump and use his hair to hover for a short period of time. He can also attack by throwing his fists, or winding up his fists for a more powerful punch. He can occasionally find special power ups that grant him unlimited flying power, giving him the ability to navigate through tricky mazes.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gbc/Rayman-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20000329T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ubisoft Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Rayman 2.gbc</path>
		<name>Rayman 2</name>
		<desc>Rayman 2 (GBC) is an adaptation of Rayman 2: The Great Escape that was released for the Game Boy Color. Despite the fact that Rayman 2 was a big hit, this game is rarely known about, even to Rayman audiences. It was released under the title Rayman 2: Forever in Europe with slightly different box art. The title screen of this game says Rayman 2: The Great Escape even though the box and the audiences regard it as Rayman 2 (GBC).</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gbc/Rayman 2-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19990106T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ubisoft</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sabrina - The Animated Series - Spooked!.gbc</path>
		<name>Sabrina the Animated Series: Spooked!</name>
		<desc>Sssomebody ssstop him! The comic book hero brought to life in inimitable fashion by Jim Carrey now has his very own handheld game on the Game Boy Color. The well being of Stanley's beloved Tina is at stake, and he's going to have to transform himself into the Mask in order to protect her. More than 20 bizarre enemies are out to stir up trouble in this bizarre epic such as motorcycle gangs, crocodile men, and others. Make your way through nine levels of excitement, using oddball weaponry like a giant boxing glove and a hunk of cheese to fend off your rivals and return Tina safely home. In addition to the standard gameplay, there are several hidden stages to uncover, most of which can be accesses by seeking out secret objects. Whether you're a fan of the comic book, the movie, or neither, you'll have your hands full with the crazy action of THE MASK.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gbc/Sabrina - The Animated Series - Spooked!-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20011106T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>WayForward Technologies</developer>
		<publisher>Simon &amp; Schuster Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sabrina - The Animated Series - Zapped!.gbc</path>
		<name>Sabrina the Animated Series: Zapped!</name>
		<desc>Sabrina has messed up again: she has turned all of the kids into animals. Now, she must travel through town and change the kids back. In order to turn the kids back, she must hit them and then use her magic on them. There are a number of power-ups available to help Sabrina on her quest, including quadruple jumps, a butt stomp, and warping abilities. She can also collect five stars that will allow her to change the kids back without having to stun them first. However, there are areas in each stage that Sabrina cannot reach. So she must find Salem, who can crawl through small spaces and use his tail to knock over blocks to clear a path for Sabrina. Getting through a level will require planning and skill, so put on your thinking cap. Help Sabrina return her classmates to normal in SABRINA THE ANIMATED SERIES: Zapped!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gbc/Sabrina - The Animated Series - Zapped!-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20001101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>WayForward Technologies</developer>
		<publisher>Simon &amp; Schuster Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Shantae.gbc</path>
		<name>Shantae</name>
		<desc>Genie-girl Shantae is the self-appointed guardian of a small fishing village, Scuttle Town. Living life in a lighthouse rather than a bottle, she's constantly on the lookout for danger. When the nefarious lady-pirate, Risky Boots catches wind of the treasure that was recently unearthed in the village, she launches an attack. To get Scuttle out of trouble, it's up to Shantae to prove that she's the rightful 'Guardian Genie' to the best of her dancing, buying and hair-whipping abilities. Now crack that whip!

* Play on the Game Boy Advance system for enhanced color and to unlock hidden secrets!
* Over 50 Locations and Mini-Games!
* Learn 'Dance Magic' to transform Shantae and learn new attacks!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gbc/Shantae-image.png</image>
		<releasedate>20020602T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>WayForward Technologies</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Space Invaders.gbc</path>
		<name>Space Invaders</name>
		<desc>Aliens are trying to take over the solar system, and you're the only one that can stop them. You are the best pilot on Earth, and you must defend all of the planets. After choosing your vehicle from the three that are available, it will stay at the bottom of the screen as a formation of aliens slowly moves down the screen. Your job is simple: blast the aliens out the sky. When they are decimated, you will move on to the next level. Fortunately, there are several power-ups available including electricity, solar flares, bubbles, shurikens, and others. As you progress through the game, new aliens with new formations will appear, not mention a boss character or two. If you are lucky enough to make it through all of the game levels, you will be able to play a version of the original arcade game released in the late '70s. Defend the Earth from tyranny in SPACE INVADERS.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gbc/Space Invaders-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19991022T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Crawfish Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./SpongeBob SquarePants - Legend of the Lost Spatula.gbc</path>
		<name>Nickelodeon SpongeBob SquarePants: Legend of the Lost Spatula</name>
		<desc>SpongeBob SquarePants makes his first appearance on Game Boy Color in the Legend of the Lost Spatula. As the wacky-but-popular character from the TV cartoon you'll head out on an undersea quest to find the Flying Dutchman's Golden Spatula in order to become the ocean's greatest short-order cook. More than 10 stages full of adventure and side-scrolling action make up this epic treasure hunt. Along the way, you'll meet and interact with many of the show's popular recurring characters like Mr. Krabs, Squidward, Sandy Cheeks, and Patrick Star. Keep an eye out for hidden clues to the Golden Spatula's whereabouts as you make your way through each stage, but also be wary of enemies and obstacles. Colorful cutscenes tell the story between levels, and you can use the password system to save your progress through the game. SPONGEBOB SQUAREPANTS: Legend of the Lost Spatula is only compatible with Game Boy Color systems.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gbc/SpongeBob SquarePants - Legend of the Lost Spatula-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20010305T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Vicarious Visions</developer>
		<publisher>THQ</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Street Fighter Alpha - Warriors' Dreams.gbc</path>
		<name>Street Fighter Alpha: Warriors' Dreams</name>
		<desc>The challenge has been made and you're cast into the battle with nothing but cunning and skill on your side. The world's most powerful collection of warriors is now assembled in one incredible tournament. Armed with an arsenal of new martial arts moves, Super Combos and Alpha Counters, legendary Street Fighters, Ryu- Chun-Li and Ken collide with a lethal new combination of foes. Welcome to the most extreme one-on-one warfare ever!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gbc/Street Fighter Alpha - Warriors' Dreams-image.png</image>
		<releasedate>20000301T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Crawfish Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Mario Bros. Deluxe.gbc</path>
		<name>Super Mario Bros. Deluxe</name>
		<desc>Bowser has once again taken over the Mushroom Kingdom, and it's up to Mario to put an end to his sinister reign. Battle Bowser's vile henchmen through 32 different levels - all taken directly from the 1985 classic! Then move on to collect special Red Coins and Yoshi Eggs in the Challenge Mode. Or face off against a friend and race through 8 competition courses in the all-new VS Mode! This time there's a lot more to do than just save a Princess, so get ready for a brick-smashin', pipe-warpin', turtle-stompin' good time!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gbc/Super Mario Bros. Deluxe-image.png</image>
		<releasedate>19990430T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tomb Raider.gbc</path>
		<name>Tomb Raider Starring Lara Croft</name>
		<desc>Now you can put Lara Croft in the palm of your hand with TOMB RAIDER for the Game Boy Color. The Aztecs, Mayas, and Incas worked together to trap an evil deity known as Quaxet in a stone that has remained undisturbed for centuries. Now, someone sinister is after the stone, and it is up to world-famous archeologist Lara Croft to find it before it falls into the wrong hands. You must guide Lara through 14 levels of action. Luckily, she can perform 25 different moves to help her get through any situation including running, jumping, crawling, and back flips. Naturally, there are people out to stop her, but they can be dispatched with a few well-placed shots from her pistols. Help Lara save the world from the power of Quaxet in TOMB RAIDER.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gbc/Tomb Raider-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20000612T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Core Design Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>THQ</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tomb Raider - Curse of the Sword.gbc</path>
		<name>Tomb Raider: Curse of the Sword</name>
		<desc>Released in conjunction with the LARA CROFT: Tomb Raider film starring Angelina Jolie, Curse of the Sword is one of the more advanced titles ever created for the Game Boy Color. While averting a museum robbery, Lara is wounded ever so slightly by what seems to be a cursed sword. Now, her worst fears are beginning to come true, as a bizarre cult based out of New Orleans is plotting to steal her soul. Help the lovely and talented Ms. Croft save herself as you control her through worldly adventures of all sorts. An equal blend of puzzle solving and action, the game boasts a unique control system that allows for maximum character response. You'll be collecting keys and artifacts throughout the experience, each of which will help you to unlock doors and secrets. Graced by perfect animation and epic gameplay, TOMB RAIDER: Curse of the Sword is a welcome addition to the long line of brilliant TOMB RAIDER games.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gbc/Tomb Raider - Curse of the Sword-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20010701T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Core Design Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tony Hawk's Pro Skater.gbc</path>
		<name>Tony Hawk's Pro Skater</name>
		<desc>Grab a skateboard and head to the streets for some action in TONY HAWK'S PRO SKATER. Try to score as many tricks as possible in the Halfpipe mode, where the biggest rewards come with complexity and originality. In the Tournament mode, you must compete against professional skaters in five different skate parks, navigating through the park and performing tricks. Hopefully, you will be able to beat the competition to the finish line. If your friends want in on the action, you can challenge them to a race with the Versus mode, where you can compete via the link cable. But don't enter the Versus mode unless you are prepared; the best preparation comes by playing the One-on-One mode against the computer. Get all of the skateboarding action you can handle with TONY HAWK'S PRO SKATER.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gbc/Tony Hawk's Pro Skater-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20000301T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Natsume</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tony Hawk's Pro Skater 2.gbc</path>
		<name>Tony Hawk's Pro Skater 2</name>
		<desc>The gameplay in this Game Boy Color adaptation of the long-running skateboarding franchise is much more akin to a balls-out side-scrolling action game than the cautious Kathy obstacle course runs of the first Tony Hawk. Developed by Japanese studio Natsume, gameplay allows several types of grinds that can link combos on the game's infinite rails, and aerial tricks are nearly as detailed as their 32-bit home boys. GBC owners can choose from 12 professional skaters and skate through seven different locations. No battery save, but the password save system supports the Game Boy Printer for easier logging.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gbc/Tony Hawk's Pro Skater 2-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20001101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Natsume</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tony Hawk's Pro Skater 3.gbc</path>
		<name>Tony Hawk's Pro Skater 3</name>
		<desc>If extreme sports games are your thing, you just can't beat the intense action and wicked tricks of the TONY HAWK'S PRO SKATER titles. Graced by incredible graphics and video effects, this chapter goes where none of the previous installments dared to go: Canada. Taking the excitement to the farthest reaches of the globe, PRO SKATER 3 also journeys to Rhode Island, Tokyo, Los Angeles, Rio, and Paris, among others. There are literally hundreds of combos and moves to pull off, and the signature control scheme has actually been improved upon this time out. Whereas previous versions of the game didn't dare leave the skate park, this one forces you to contend with everyday obstacles like pedestrians, traffic, natural disasters, and more. The visual presentation, sound effects, cadre of top-notch professional skaters, and spectrum of tricks has all been improved upon here making for the best TONY HAWK'S PRO SKATER yet.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gbc/Tony Hawk's Pro Skater 3-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20011115T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>HotGen Studios</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Wario Land 2.gbc</path>
		<name>Wario Land 3</name>
		<desc>Trapped inside a magical music box, the invincible Wario is on a dangerous quest to help a mysterious figure recover its lost powers! Smash, bash and crash your way through more than two dozen gigantic levels in search of hidden keys, valuable treasures and mystical music boxes. Test your wits on puzzle after intricate puzzle and flex your muscles in action-packed boss fights! Be wary of Wanderin' Gooms, Hammer-bots, Mad Scienstein and more as you plunge into one of the largest, most dazzling adventures ever to hit Game Boy Color!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gbc/Wario Land 2-image.png</image>
		<releasedate>20000501T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Yu-Gi-Oh! - Dark Duel Stories.gbc</path>
		<name>Yu-Gi-Oh! Dark Duel Stories</name>
		<desc>The third GB version of Yu-Gi-Oh! Duel Monsters. Over 10,000 types of cards! !! From this time, it fully supports the expert rules of official card games. By adopting expert rules, Duel's strategy is the best in card games! The effects of ikenie and magic cards are also reproduced perfectly. In addition, it is full of new elements such as the original deck capacity, level, and original cards of the GB version. Equipped with "card construction" that allows you to create your own original card. The first limited edition always comes with 4 out of 9 cards!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gbc/Yu-Gi-Oh! - Dark Duel Stories-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20020318T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Bugs Bunny - Crazy Castle 3.gbc</path>
		<name>Bugs Bunny In Crazy Castle 3</name>
		<desc>Bugs Bunny returns to crazy puzzle or action gaming on Game boy Color. Once again you play as the legendary Bugs Bunny as he explores the mysterious Crazy Castle in search of the mother lode of carrots. The castle has all-new rooms with all-new puzzles, so prepare yourself for even more hare-brained action than the last time around. The Crazy Castle is chock-full of hazards and traps that will end your merry little jaunt in a hurry, so keep a sharp eye out. In order to test your reflexes as well as your wits, several Warner Bros. cartoon characters have returned to make Bugs's life that much more difficult! Fight off Sylvester, Daffy Duck, Yosemite Sam, Elmer Fudd, Tweety Bird, and the Tazmanian Devil with one of your weapons, or just turn tail and run as fast as you can. Naturally, the game comes complete with a password function so you can explore the floors at your leisure once you've cleared them.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gbc/Bugs Bunny - Crazy Castle 3-image.png</image>
		<releasedate>19990101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Kemco</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20210313T070902</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Wario Land 3.gbc</path>
		<name>Wario Land 3</name>
		<desc>Trapped inside a magical music box, the invincible Wario is on a dangerous quest to help a mysterious figure recover its lost powers! Smash, bash and crash your way through more than two dozen gigantic levels in search of hidden keys, valuable treasures and mystical music boxes. Test your wits on puzzle after intricate puzzle and flex your muscles in action-packed boss fights! Be wary of Wanderin' Gooms, Hammer-bots, Mad Scienstein and more as you plunge into one of the largest, most dazzling adventures ever to hit Game Boy Color!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gbc/Wario Land 3-image.png</image>
		<releasedate>20000501T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20210405T053939</lastplayed>
	</game>
</gameList>
