<?xml version="1.0"?>
<gameList>
	<game>
		<path>./Children of Mana (E)(FireX).nds</path>
		<name>Children of Mana (E)(FireX)</name>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19700101T000000</releasedate>
		<hidden>true</hidden>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Undertale DS.nds</path>
		<name>Undertale DS</name>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19700101T000000</releasedate>
		<hidden>true</hidden>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20201110T012433</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Advance Wars - Dual Strike.nds</path>
		<name>Advance Wars: Dual Strike</name>
		<desc>Advance Wars: Dual Strike is the third installment in the Advance Wars series (first on DS media). Advance Wars is the international title of the Wars video game series, which dates back to the Family Computer game Famicom Wars in 1988.
The storyline is a continuation of the previous series and is set in the new location of Omega Land. Black Hole has returned under the leadership of a new commander who seeks to give himself eternal life by draining the energy of Omega Land. The Allied Nations struggle to overcome this threat and are eventually joined by several former Black Hole commanding officers in an effort to save the land.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Advance Wars - Dual Strike-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20050822T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Intelligent Systems Co., Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Adventure Time - Hey Ice King! Why'd you Steal our Garbage!!.nds</path>
		<name>Adventure Time: Hey Ice King! Why'd You Steal Our Garbage?!!</name>
		<desc>Adventure Time: Hey Ice King! Why'd you steal our garbage?! is the first video game based on the radical, Emmy nominated Cartoon Network show about two close friends - Jake, a wise old dog with a big kind heart, and Finn, a silly kid who wants more than anything else to become a great hero. Players will explore the Land of Ooo and set out on heroic quests, as their favorite characters Finn and Jake, in a unique action adventure experience. Adventure Time show creator Pendleton Ward is also heavily involved with the game creation, including the design of a brand new storyline, concept, and quests.

Finn and Jake wake up one morning to find their trash stolen by the Ice King! Jake couldn't care less about half-eaten bananas, crumpled up math notes, and old chicken diapers - but when the Ice King uses these stolen goods to construct a Garbage Princess, our heroes embark on a fantastical adventure and teach him a lesson! Journey through the Land of Ooo in an offbeat adventure and discover perilous dungeons, unimaginable treasures, the true meaning of friendship, and never-ending fun!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Adventure Time - Hey Ice King! Why'd you Steal our Garbage!!-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20121120T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>WayForward Technologies</developer>
		<publisher>Bandai Namco Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Animal Crossing - Wild World.nds</path>
		<name>Animal Crossing: Wild World</name>
		<desc>Animal Crossing: Wild World (おいでよ どうぶつの森 Oideyo Dōbutsu no mori?, "Come to Animal Forest") is a 2005 social simulation video game developed and published by Nintendo for the Nintendo DS handheld game console, and is the second game in the Animal Crossing series.

Wild World focuses on living in a remote village populated with anthropomorphic animals, where the player is encouraged to perform any number of tasks, such as collecting and planting. Like all Animal Crossing titles, the game is synced to the console's clock and calendar, allowing the game to be played in real-time, which affects the occurrence of in-game events based on the current time of day or season. Wild World also utilizes Nintendo Wi-Fi Connection, which notably allows players to travel and visit the villages of other players via online play.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Animal Crossing - Wild World-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20051205T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Life Simulation</genre>
		<players>4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Assassin's Creed - Altair's Chronicles.nds</path>
		<name>Assassin's Creed: Altair's Chronicles</name>
		<desc>Assassin's Creed: Altaïr's Chronicles is a prequel to the 2007 video game Assassin's Creed. 
It takes advantage of the Nintendo DS features. The game's main gameplay featured a 3D platform-puzzle game format with third person hack-and-slash combat and more limited stealth maneuvering. The touchscreen is utilized for mini-games, like interrogation and pickpocketing, as well as displaying a map during standard gameplay. The game's combat system consists primarily of weak attacks, strong attacks, blocks, and combos of the three with the sword, while bombs and projectiles are made available in later gameplay. Seven different weapons are available, including the hidden retractable blade, a sword, crossbow, explosive bombs, smoke bombs, and throwing knives. The game also features three different levels of difficulty, allowing for more experienced players to take on a bigger challenge.
It features five cities, Tyre and Aleppo, Jerusalem, Acre and Damascus. Unlike the original Assassin's Creed, the game is not told through the perspective of Desmond Miles, but rather the perspective of Altaïr Ibn La-Ahad, although the menu screens do take place in the Animus.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Assassin's Creed - Altair's Chronicles-image.png</image>
		<releasedate>20080205T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Gameloft S.A.</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure, Stealth</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Assassin's Creed II - Discovery.nds</path>
		<name>Assassin's Creed II: Discovery</name>
		<desc>Assassin's Creed II: Discovery, in contrast to Altaïr's Chronicles, the previous title in the Assassin's Creed series to be on the DS, is a 2.5D side-scroller.
The game's story takes place 14 years after the beginning of its console counterpart, Assassin's Creed II. It follows that game's protagonist, Ezio Auditore da Firenze, as he travels to 15th century Spain to free his fellow assassins, who have been imprisoned under the guise of the Spanish Inquisition.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Assassin's Creed II - Discovery-image.png</image>
		<releasedate>20091117T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Griptonite Games</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure, Stealth</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Avalon Code.nds</path>
		<name>Avalon Code</name>
		<desc>Avalon Code plot, as well as the gameplay, revolves around the Book of Prophecy situated on the touch-sensitive lower screen of the Nintendo DS. In order to record a person, monster, plant, or weapon in its pages, the player performs a “Code Scan”, which is done by striking the target to be recorded with the Book itself (mapped to the B button at all times). The story centers on a young peasant who has been plagued with prophetic nightmares for weeks prior to the beginning of the story. His or her latest dream, shown in the opening cinematic, features a mysterious voice which reveals not only that the protagonist's world has undergone countless reincarnations in the past and is fated to continue the cycle of correction, destruction, and rebirth until “true enlightenment” is achieved, but also that the main character him- or herself has been tasked by the Powers-That-Be to deem the people, places, and things of the current world worthy (or unworthy) of being carried over into the next after the fiery purge.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Avalon Code-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20090310T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Matrix Software</developer>
		<publisher>XSEED Games</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Avatar - The Last Airbender - Into the Inferno.nds</path>
		<name>Avatar: The Last Airbender - Into the Inferno</name>
		<desc>The Fire Nation devises a plot to use the power of Sozin's Comet to rain devastation on the rest of the world. The fate of the world lies in the hands of only a few young, brave heroes -- Aang and his friends. They are preparing for the ultimate showdown against Fire Lord Ozai and his terrorizing army that will ultimately decide who will win the great 100 year old war.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Avatar - The Last Airbender - Into the Inferno-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20081013T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Halfbrick Studios</developer>
		<publisher>THQ</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Avatar - The Last Airbender - The Burning Earth.nds</path>
		<name>Avatar: The Last Airbender - The Burning Earth</name>
		<desc>Journey through 6 exotic locations filled with adventure to help Aang fulfill his destiny to master the bending arts and become the Avatar—for only the Avatar can stop the ruthless might of the Fire Nation! Defeat hordes of bizarre enemies and perform noble deeds on your quest to save the world.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Avatar - The Last Airbender - The Burning Earth-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20071016T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>THQ</developer>
		<publisher>THQ</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ben 10 - Alien Force.nds</path>
		<name>Ben 10: Alien Force</name>
		<desc>Explore action packed levels as Ben and fight off alien enemies including the HighBreed and DNAliens. Play as favorite alien heroes including Big Chill, Swampfire, Humungousaur and more! Exclusive alien heroes Goop, Echo Echo and ChromaStone are playable on the Nintendo DS!

    Command members of the ALIEN FORCE team - Investigate never-before-seen locations, enemies and characters, and explore favorite places from show episodes
    Multiple playable characters – Take control of Ben and his new alien forms Swampfire, Humungousaur, Big Chill, Jet Ray and Spidermonkey
    Alternate playable alien heroes Goop, Echo Echo and ChromaStone exclusive to the DS version
    Solid and robust gameplay – Use more than 75 attack options and create unlimited attack chaining with the streamlined combo system
    Art style, sound effects, and music are 100% authentic - All audio pulled directly from the show sound vaults</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Ben 10 - Alien Force-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20081028T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>1st Playable Productions</developer>
		<publisher>D3 Publisher Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ben 10 - Alien Force - Vilgax Attacks.nds</path>
		<name>Ben 10 Alien Force: Vilgax Attacks</name>
		<desc>The latest game in the multimillion-unit-selling Ben 10 video game franchise based on Cartoon Network's hit television show, BEN 10: ALIEN FORCE Vilgax Attacks puts players in control of Ben Tennyson on a journey to outer space and distant never-before-seen planets for the first time ever in the series. As in the show, Ben will use 10 of his alien forms and their special powers to battle his greatest enemy, Vilgax, and an extreme team of fearsome foes in an effort to thwart a grand scheme to conquer the universe one planet at a time.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Ben 10 - Alien Force - Vilgax Attacks-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20091027T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Papaya Studios</developer>
		<publisher>D3 Publisher Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure, Fighting</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ben 10 - Galactic Racing.nds</path>
		<name>Ben 10: Galactic Racing</name>
		<desc>The first kart racing game set in the popular BEN 10 universe and based on the hit Cartoon Network TV series features Ben and his alien friends competing in an over-the-top, galactic grand prix race through a variety of tracks on five different planets! Compete for the best times in the high-speed grand prix modes or engage in four-player multiplayer mayhem!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Ben 10 - Galactic Racing-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20111018T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Monkey Bar Games, Tantalus Media</developer>
		<publisher>D3 Publisher Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Racing, Sports</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ben 10 - Omniverse.nds</path>
		<name>Ben 10: Omniverse</name>
		<desc>Ben 10: Omniverse is the only video game based on the highly-anticipated, Cartoon Network TV series, Ben 10: Omniverse. The brand-new show spans two time periods between Young and Teen Ben Tennyson, and introduces a hero sidekick, Rook.

 In the new action game, players can play as both Young and Teen Ben, switch forms between 13 playable alien heroes, including new aliens like Bloxx and Gravattack, and fight in an assortment of action-packed levels throughout the subterranean alien city of Undertown and other show-inspired locales. In Ben: 10 Omniverse, Rook will also star in the game come equipped with a Proto-Tool, a swiss army knife of the future, that can transform into a variety of weapons that will bring a whole new dimension to combat</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Ben 10 - Omniverse-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20121113T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>1st Playable Productions, Vicious Cycle Software, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>D3 Publisher Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ben 10 - Protector of Earth.nds</path>
		<name>Ben 10: Protector of Earth</name>
		<desc>Players will take on the role of Cartoon Network's popular everyday-kid-turned-alien-hero, Ben Tennyson. Using the power of the Omnitrix which has embedded itself on Ben's wrist, players will be able to battle as one of five popular alien heroes from the show. By taking on these amazing powers, players can battle to save the world through the game's diverse challenges, puzzles and skirmishes.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Ben 10 - Protector of Earth-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20071030T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>1st Playable Productions</developer>
		<publisher>D3 Publisher Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ben 10 - Ultimate Alien - Cosmic Destruction.nds</path>
		<name>Ben 10 Ultimate Alien: Cosmic Destruction</name>
		<desc>Ben 10: Ultimate Alien-Cosmic Destruction is a video game based on Ben 10: Ultimate Alien and is the fifth game in the Ben 10 video games series.

The game was panned by reviews, being criticized by its limited length, game mechanics, as well as several gameplay and design concepts.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Ben 10 - Ultimate Alien - Cosmic Destruction-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20101005T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Papaya Studios</developer>
		<publisher>D3 Publisher Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure, Fighting</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Blue Dragon Awakened Shadow.nds</path>
		<name>Blue Dragon: Awakened Shadow</name>
		<desc>Blue Dragon: Awakened Shadow is an epic action role-playing game and the sequel to the critically acclaimed and successful Xbox 360 title. The player, aided by a young boy named Shu and his friends, will possess the power to control phantom shadows that mirror the actions of their masters, giving its owner miraculous strength and magical powers.
For the first time in the series, players will create and guide their own hero on a grand adventure to investigate the disappearance of the Shadows and bring order to their world.
Play as a new hero. For the first time in the series, the player can create their own hero and choose to journey as themselves
Deep character customization. Choose your characters gender, hairstyle, facial detail, as well as upgradeable equipment and armor which are visually reflected in the characters appearance
New strategies with Shadow Powers. Players can change their Shadows to tactically overcome the games many challenges and formidable bosses</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Blue Dragon Awakened Shadow-image.png</image>
		<releasedate>20100518T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tri-crescendo</developer>
		<publisher>D3 Publisher Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing, Strategy</genre>
		<players>4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Blue Dragon Plus.nds</path>
		<name>Blue Dragon Plus</name>
		<desc>The DS sequel is set one year after the original Xbox 360 title and returns players to the story of Shu and his companions, who control powerful phantom shadows. In the DS title, they will have to deal with new enemies spawned from the devastation wrought in the first title. At first glance, you might mistakenly believe Blue Dragon Plus to be a strategy game in the style of Final Fantasy Tactics, with little hand-drawn heroes and monsters arranged on an isometric 3D stage. But once the fight begins, everything starts happening in real time and you must feverishly put together your plan of attack, because those enemies aren't waiting for your turn. You command your units around the field with quick but simple controls that rely totally on the touch screen. You tell your units where to go, who to fight, when to heal, and when to move to special areas on the map. It seems like your attention is constantly needed everywhere at once, but the game gives you some room for error by providing a high number of healing items. Also, as you progress through each map, the game occasionally pauses to let some part of the story play out. The game will feature a thirty-hour quest as well as the ability to control up to sixteen humans and Mecha Robos in real-time battles and shadow fights.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Blue Dragon Plus-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20090219T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ignition Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Feel Plus</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing, Strategy</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Bomberman.nds</path>
		<name>Bomberman</name>
		<desc>Bomberman arrives on the DS with a variety of gameplay modes, touch screen functionality, and voice support. Using only one game card, you and seven of your friends can lay bombs in different arenas rife with power-ups. In single-player mode, you can test your reflexes and strategies through 100 stages of challenging puzzles.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Bomberman-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20050621T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Racjin Co., Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle, Strategy</genre>
		<players>4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Bomberman Land Touch!.nds</path>
		<name>Bomberman Land Touch!</name>
		<desc>The fun of the Bomberman series returns to the Nintendo DS, this time with not only classic Bomberman gameplay, but a whole new selection of addictive mini games to play alone, or over Nintendo's Wi-Fi connection! Navigate your way through an amusement park filled with addictive mini games with intuitive stylus control, while working to unlock all the games.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Bomberman Land Touch!-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20061117T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hudson Entertainment, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Atlus Co., Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Bomberman Land Touch! 2.nds</path>
		<name>Bomberman Land Touch! 2</name>
		<desc>BOMBERMAN LAND Touch! 2 is the follow up sequel to IGN's Best Online Multiplayer 2006 Game of the Year on the Nintendo DS. Embark on a fun-filled, theme park adventure as you discover a huge land to explore, a gigantic multiplayer pack, and a host of addicting mini-games that can be played by yourself or with up to 4 people.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Bomberman Land Touch! 2-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20080129T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hudson Entertainment, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Hudson Entertainment, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Bubble Bobble - Double Shot.nds</path>
		<name>Bubble Bobble: Double Shot</name>
		<desc>Bub and Bob are back! Bubble Bobble Double Shot is a respectful return to the series' roots, bringing Bubble Bobble to the DS with new additions to the classic formula. Based on the original Bubble Bobble arcade game first released in 1986, Bubble Bobble Double Shot stars the two Bubble Dragons, Bub and Bob who move over a system of platforms, busting and pushing bubbles, avoiding enemies and collecting a variety of power-ups. Bubble Bobble Double Shot for DS features a perfect re-creation of Bubble Bobble's frantic platforming gameplay, complete with all the secrets and fun gameplay that made the original such a rewarding game to master.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Bubble Bobble - Double Shot-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20080226T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Dreams</developer>
		<publisher>Ignition</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle, Platform</genre>
		<players>3</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Bubble Bobble Revolution.nds</path>
		<name>Bubble Bobble Revolution</name>
		<desc>Originally released as an arcade game by Taito in 1986, Bubble Bobble starred two dinosaurs - Bub and Bob who co-operate to make their way through a hundred levels to rescue their girlfriends. This addictive two player game went on to be released on most console formats. Now the game is reborn on the Nintendo DS with all new graphics, split screen action and the classic gameplay. 100 new exciting levels to explore. All new power bubbles and bubble attacks. Microphone activated challenges and Bubble mini-games. Includes a perfect re-creation of the original Bubble Bobble arcade machine game.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Bubble Bobble Revolution-image.png</image>
		<releasedate>20060929T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Dreams</developer>
		<publisher>Taito Corporation</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Puzzle</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Call of Duty - Black Ops.nds</path>
		<name>Call of Duty: Black Ops</name>
		<desc>Call of Duty: Black Ops has many new features like the Perks system for the six player online multiplayer. N-Space announced that the multiplayer experience has changed dramatically. The game also has a unique two player co-op.

For players who do not like to aim with the stylus, there is an alternative control scheme. There is also an improved user interface. The player can tap an icon to switch the current weapon for a new one, like past DS games, or drag the weapon into an inactive button to add to their inventory without replacing the weapon they are using currently. An auto lock-on feature is available to use in the Recruit and Regular difficulties.

The player also takes control of an attack helicopter and an experimental stealth fighter jet.

The Arcade and Challenges modes will be returning. The game also features achievements.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Call of Duty - Black Ops-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20101109T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>n-Space, Inc</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Shooter</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Call of Duty - Modern Warfare - Mobilized.nds</path>
		<name>Call of Duty: Modern Warfare - Mobilized</name>
		<desc>From Wikipedia:

Call of Duty: Modern Warfare: Mobilized is a 2009 first person shooter video game in the Call of Duty franchise, developed specifically for the Nintendo DS. The game takes place in the same setting as Call of Duty: Modern Warfare 2 and features many elements of gameplay typical to the series, including the usage of iron sights, and vehicular missions. It was released by Activision alongside the console versions of the game on November 10, 2009.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Call of Duty - Modern Warfare - Mobilized-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20091110T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>n-Space, Inc</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Shooter</genre>
		<players>4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Call of Duty - Modern Warfare 3 - Defiance.nds</path>
		<name>Call of Duty: Modern Warfare 3 - Defiance</name>
		<desc>Call of Duty: Modern Warfare 3 is the 2011 release in the best-selling Call of Duty First-Person Shooter action series. The game is a direct sequel to the previous game in the series, Call of Duty: Modern Warfare 2, with a campaign storyline continuing the struggle of U.S. forces against an invasion by the Russian Federation following the framing of an undercover U.S. agent in a terrorist attack on Moscow. Along with classic Call of Duty multi-character control, Call of Duty: Modern Warfare 3 contains deep multiplayer support, including two-player Co-op Survival mode. The game also contains all-new Kill Streak categories and customizable strike packages that offer more options for player combat styles and strategies.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Call of Duty - Modern Warfare 3 - Defiance-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20111108T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>n-Space, Inc</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Shooter</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Cartoon Network Racing.nds</path>
		<name>Cartoon Network Racing</name>
		<desc>Cartoon Network Racing provides gamers with endless hours of fun with 24 different racing circuits for players to zoom round. Racing zones include Spooky Mine and the Theme Park, plus -show-themed- locations such as Dexter's Laboratory and the Aron City. Players can enjoy the game alone in single player mode, or go head-to-head with an opponent or race as driver and co-driver in the two-player mode.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Cartoon Network Racing-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20061130T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Firebrand Games</developer>
		<publisher>Game Factory Interactive Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Castlevania - Dawn of Sorrow.nds</path>
		<name>Castlevania: Dawn of Sorrow</name>
		<desc>The team that developed Castlevania: Aria of Sorrow returns to bring the sequel, CastleVania: Dawn of Sorrow, to the Nintendo DS. This time, you must infiltrate a castle belonging to a cult that is planning to resurrect Lord Dracula. Castlevania: Dawn of Sorrow lets you defeat evil spirits using the "Magic Seal" system which utilizes the Nintendo DS touch screen. You can trade captured souls with other players using the wireless system as well.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Castlevania - Dawn of Sorrow-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20051004T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure, Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Castlevania - Order of Ecclesia.nds</path>
		<name>Castlevania: Order of Ecclesia</name>
		<desc>Following the success of Dawn of Sorrow and Portrait of Ruin, the legendary Castlevania series is back on the Nintendo DS. This time you play as a member of the Ecclesia, an organization that has sworn to defeat the evil forces of Dracula. Use the brand new Glyph attack system which has more than 100 different combinations to battle Dracula and his minions throughout 20 explorable areas. Take part in side quests and collect items to power up your character in the next great Castlevania game produced by Koji Igarashi.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Castlevania - Order of Ecclesia-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20081021T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure, Platform</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Castlevania - Portrait of Ruin.nds</path>
		<name>Castlevania: Portrait of Ruin</name>
		<desc>Celebrating 20 years of vampire hunting action, the legendary Castlevania series is back with an all-new action packed adventure. Take control of two heroes, Jonathan Morris, a vampire killer and his close friend Charlotte Orlean, a girl with tremendous magical ability. Amidst the chaos of World War II, two mysterious sisters emerge, working to resurrect Dracula and David and Charlotte are all that stand in their way.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Castlevania - Portrait of Ruin-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20061116T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure, Platform</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Children of Mana.nds</path>
		<name>Children of Mana</name>
		<desc>This installment of the series takes place in the world of Fa'diel on the island of Illusia where, at the center of the island, stands the famous Tree of Mana. Several years ago, on the island of Illusia, an event known the "great disaster" took place at the base of the Mana Tree and many lives were lost. During this event, a brave young boy and girl used the Sword of Mana to save the world from disaster. Now, years later, a group of orphans sets out to investigate the details of the event that took so many loved ones away from them. The player must journey through the rest of Fa'diel's five continents of Jadd, Topple, Wendell, Ishe, and Lorimar to complete the game, traveling to the other continents by riding Flammie from place to place using the "Flammie Drum."</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Children of Mana-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20060302T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Square Enix</developer>
		<publisher>Square Enix</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Chrono Trigger.nds</path>
		<name>Chrono Trigger</name>
		<desc>Chrono Trigger features standard console role-playing game (RPG) gameplay with several innovations. The player controls the protagonist and his companions in the game's two-dimensional fictional world, consisting of various forests, cities, and dungeons. Navigation occurs via an overworld map, depicting the landscape from a scaled down overhead view. Areas such as forests, cities, and similar places are depicted as more realistic scaled down maps, in which players can converse with locals to procure items and services, solve puzzles and challenges, or encounter enemies. Chrono Trigger's gameplay deviates from that of traditional RPGs in that, rather than appearing in random encounters, many enemies are openly visible on field maps or lie in wait to ambush the party. Contact with enemies on a field map initiates a battle that occurs directly on the map rather than on a separate battle screen.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Chrono Trigger-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20081125T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Square Enix</developer>
		<publisher>Square Enix</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Contra 4.nds</path>
		<name>Contra 4</name>
		<desc>The action franchise that started it all is celebrating its 20th anniversary with an all-new adventure on Nintendo DS! Set after the events of Contra III: Alien Wars, the game follows mercenaries Bill Rizer and Lance Bean as they battle to save the world from a new extraterrestrial threat. Contra 4 takes advantage of the dual screens of the Nintendo DS to deliver larger than life action, with massive enemies, detailed platforming and mind-blowing set pieces.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Contra 4-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20071113T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>WayForward Technologies</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Shooter, Platform</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Cooking Mama 2 - Dinner with Friends.nds</path>
		<name>Cooking Mama 2: Dinner with Friends</name>
		<desc>As in the original The Cooking Mama, players in The Cooking Mama 2: Dinner with Friends, prepare various culinary dishes using the Nintendo DS's touch screen. Following the on-screen instructions of the titular "Mama", the player uses the stylus to perform various activities such as chopping vegetables or mixing ingredients. Each of these tasks is performed by completing a short minigame, with a number of minigames strung together to form an entire dish from a catalog of 80 different recipes.

After completing a dish, the player's cooking performance is evaluated and given a numerical score (out of 100) along with a corresponding medal. Failing to accomplish a step in Let's Cook mode or getting a "fail" within steps (in various ranges), the player will receive a "Broken Silver" medal, in which the medal is similar to that of the Silver medal with an addition: a crack. Unlike in previous Cooking Mama titles, bonuses earned during minigames do not influence the overall score, but instead accumulate as "bonus stars". For every 5 such bonuses which are earned, the player earns an unlockable item upon completion of the recipe.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Cooking Mama 2 - Dinner with Friends-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20071113T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Office Create</developer>
		<publisher>Majesco Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Life Simulation</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Cooking Mama 3 - Shop &amp; Chop.nds</path>
		<name>Cooking Mama 3: Shop &amp; Chop</name>
		<desc>In Cooking Mama 3, players use the stylus as the ultimate cooking utensil to create 80 all new dishes including chili con carne, tulip chicken, mushroom quiche and more. For the first time players can shop for the necessary ingredients before they start cooking in 200 different mini-games that let them chop, grate, slice, and stir up phenomenal foods. Cooking Mama 3 also lets aspiring chefs create their own dishes by combining ingredients together in delicious new ways. In addition, the game features multiplayer cooking challenges and five other gameplay modes. As recipes progress from simple to complex and from small to large dishes, players must do their best to meet Mama's expectations and impress their hungry friends. If friends think a dish is delicious, gamers will get to unlock another new friend!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Cooking Mama 3 - Shop &amp; Chop-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20091020T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Cooking Mama Limited</developer>
		<publisher>Majesco Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Crash - Mind Over Mutant.nds</path>
		<name>Crash: Mind Over Mutant</name>
		<desc>In Crash Bandicoot: Mind Over Mutant, a rejuvenated Neo Cortex is taking over the world one brain at a time! Cortex and N. Brio devise a new kind of evil: a text-messaging, do-anything device that controls both mutant and bandicoot minds. Armed with his quick wits and lightning agility, Crash must free his friends, the titans, and save the day!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Crash - Mind Over Mutant-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20081007T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Radical Entertainment Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Activision Blizzard, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Crash Boom Bang!.nds</path>
		<name>Crash Boom Bang!</name>
		<desc>Crash Boom Bang! (known in Japan as Crash Bandicoot Festival) (クラッシュ・バンディクー フェスティバル Kurasshu Bandikū Fesutibaru?) is a party game developed by Dimps and published by Vivendi Universal Games in Japan and by Sierra Entertainment internationally for the Nintendo DS. It was released in Japan on July 20, 2006, in North America on October 10, 2006,[1] in Europe on October 27, 2006, and in Australia on November 2, 2006.[3] It is the only game in the Crash Bandicoot series to be developed by a Japanese company and the first to be released in Japan before North America. It was also the final game in the series to be released in Japan.

Crash Boom Bang! is the first game to be released exclusively for the Nintendo DS, and the second party game of the series, after Crash Bash. The game's story centers on a multi-millionaire who uses the characters of the series to unearth a powerful object dubbed the "Super Big Power Crystal". The game has received largely negative reception from reviewers, who criticized it for having unoriginal, dull gameplay and poor controls.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Crash Boom Bang!-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20061010T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Dimps Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>Sierra</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Crash of the Titans.nds</path>
		<name>Crash of the Titans</name>
		<desc>In Crash of the Titans, players fight a nefarious plot hatched by Crash's arch nemeses Neo and Nina Cortex to mutate the local creatures into titanic abominations. Using Crash's legendary mix of outrageous antics and daredevil bravado, players "hijack" enemies to take control of their action and use their fearsome powers against all manner of enemies. "Jack to Attack!" – Control, play and battle as 15 enemies, including titanic creatures such as Scorporilla, Ratcicle, Magamadon and Shellephant. While in control of a monster players can throw toxic stink bombs, call lightning down from the sky, fire lasers beams from their eyes or even impale enemies with a massive scorpion tail - use all of the creatures' special abilities to defeat Neo and Nina Cortex. Crash now has a powerful acrobatic fighting system that includes punches and flying kicks, multiple attacks and special counter moves.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Crash of the Titans-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20071002T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Amaze Entertainment, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Sierra</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Diner Dash - Flo on the Go.nds</path>
		<name>Diner Dash: Flo on the Go</name>
		<desc>The famous Flo is back but this time she's traded in her apron for a passport to paradise! With all the hustle and bustle ... will our hard-working waitress get a chance to relax? Help Flo seat customers, take orders, collect tips and dress her up in hundreds of vacation outfits in the all-new Flo's Closet. New thrills, spills, and a surprise restaurant await you in the third episode of the original smash hit.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Diner Dash - Flo on the Go-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20091103T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>PlayFirst</developer>
		<publisher>Zoo Games</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Diner Dash - Sizzle &amp; Serve.nds</path>
		<name>Diner Dash: Sizzle &amp; Serve</name>
		<desc>In Diner Dash, you play the restaurant entrepreneur Flo, out to work her way up to the top of the food service industry. The game blends fast-paced action puzzles with a build-your-restaurant-empire theme through over 40 different levels.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Diner Dash - Sizzle &amp; Serve-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20070523T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Climax Studios</developer>
		<publisher>Eidos Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Puzzle</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dogz.nds</path>
		<name>Dogz</name>
		<desc>A pet simulation game that lets owners name, train and play with a realistic puppy. Players create and control a main character and choose one of 49 different dogs from 18 different breeds. As characters in the game, owners can take their puppies everywhere within the virtual environment, from through the house to around the neighborhood to visit friends. Gamers will earn their puppy-s love and loyalty by remembering to feed and groom it and reward it when it does things correctly. Owners can train the puppy to lie down, shake, fetch and perform many other tricks.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Dogz-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20061122T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>MTO</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Life Simulation</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dragon Ball - Origins.nds</path>
		<name>Dragon Ball: Origins</name>
		<desc>Dragon Ball: Origins follows Goku and his clever sidekick Bulma as they travel the world overcoming enemies and obstacles to collect the 7 Dragon Balls. In the shoes of Goku, the player must protect Bulma from incoming enemy attacks using special skills, such as fighting with his power pole, or unleashing a kamehameha. Combined with Bulma’s ability to invent machines and weapons, the intrepid pair make a formidable team able to defeat even the strongest enemies or trickiest of obstacles.

The innovative controls mean the player uses only the touch pad to control Goku. Players must draw lines or shapes to direct the character and control the action by tapping on the screen, for example a double tap on Goku followed by tapping on the Ka-me-ha-me-ha letters unleashes his devastating signature move.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Dragon Ball - Origins-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20081104T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Game Republic</developer>
		<publisher>Atari SA</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dragon Quest Heroes - Rocket Slime.nds</path>
		<name>Dragon Quest Heroes: Rocket Slime</name>
		<desc>Dragon Quest Heroes: Rocket Slime is based in the fictional world of Slimenia, specifically in the capital city of Boingburg. It begins with four Slimes, Rocket, Hooly, Bo, and Swotsy, who are playing in front of the castle. Hooly has gotten his hands on a valuable flute, and in response to the flute being blown by Rocket, his father comes running over, forcing Hooly to stick the flute in Rocket's mouth. Afterward, an organization known as the Plob invades Boingburg, capturing 100 of its 101 inhabitants. Because he was distorted and long, the Plob mistakenly believed Rocket was not a Slime but a worm, and discarded him into Forewood Forest. There, Rocket begins his journey to rescue his fellow slimes, who have been locked up in large treasure chests.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Dragon Quest Heroes - Rocket Slime-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20060919T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tose Co., Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Square Enix</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dragon Quest IV - Chapters of the Chosen.nds</path>
		<name>Dragon Quest IV: Chapters of the Chosen</name>
		<desc>The Legends of Zenithia starts here!

A prestigious army captain, an adventurous princess, a humble merchant, two sisters, and you, the hero. Dive into this unique adventure, and discover the grand tale told through the experiences and emotions of characters from all walks of life.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Dragon Quest IV - Chapters of the Chosen-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20080916T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>ArtePiazza</developer>
		<publisher>Squaresoft</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dragon Quest IX - Sentinels of the Starry Skies.nds</path>
		<name>Dragon Quest IX: Sentinels of the Starry Skies</name>
		<desc>In Dragon Quest IX: Sentinels of the Starry Skies, players begin their adventure as a city guardian who is sent to retrieve a sacred trees fruits, which have the power to grant wishes. Players travel the world, conquer fearsome monsters and unravel an epic storyline. During their journey, players will encounter mighty opponents in fast-paced battles, and also interact with a colorful cast of characters.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Dragon Quest IX - Sentinels of the Starry Skies-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20100711T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Level-5</developer>
		<publisher>Square Enix</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
		<players>4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dragon Quest Monsters - Joker.nds</path>
		<name>Dragon Quest Monsters: Joker</name>
		<desc>Players assume the role of a monster hunter as they capture, train and breed a powerful army from more than 200 classic Dragon Quest creatures in order to become the world's greatest monster trainer. Joker is a breakout title that combines the depth of a classic Dragon Quest RPG with the addictiveness of a monster catching adventure.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Dragon Quest Monsters - Joker-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20071106T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Square Enix</developer>
		<publisher>Square Enix</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dragon Quest Monsters - Joker 2.nds</path>
		<name>Dragon Quest Monsters: Joker</name>
		<desc>Players assume the role of a monster hunter as they capture, train and breed a powerful army from more than 200 classic Dragon Quest creatures in order to become the world's greatest monster trainer. Joker is a breakout title that combines the depth of a classic Dragon Quest RPG with the addictiveness of a monster catching adventure.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Dragon Quest Monsters - Joker 2-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20071106T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Square Enix</developer>
		<publisher>Square Enix</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dragon Quest V - Hand of the Heavenly Bride.nds</path>
		<name>Dragon Quest V: Hand of the Heavenly Bride</name>
		<desc>The legend of Zenithia continues!

What begins as an innocent voyage of a boy traveling alongside his father develops into an eye-opening adventure that transcends generations. You - a hero in the making - determine your own path, choose your own wife and befriend a wagonload of quirky monsters along the way.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Dragon Quest V - Hand of the Heavenly Bride-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20090217T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>ArtePiazza</developer>
		<publisher>Square Enix</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dragon Quest VI - Realms of Revelation.nds</path>
		<name>Dragon Quest VI: Realms of Revelation</name>
		<desc>Coming to North America for the first time, Dragon Quest VI: Realms of Revelation for Nintendo DS brings the classic console title into the handheld scene. Explore two parallel worlds while distinguishing reality from illusion and seeking to discover the true meaning of your very existence.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Dragon Quest VI - Realms of Revelation-image.png</image>
		<releasedate>20110214T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>ArtePiazza</developer>
		<publisher>Squaresoft</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Drawn to Life.nds</path>
		<name>Drawn to Life</name>
		<desc>Drawn to Life is an action-adventure platform video game for the Nintendo DS developed by 5th Cell and published by THQ in 2007.[4] It was later published by Agatsuma Entertainment in Japan in 2008 under the name Drawn to Life: God's Marionette (ドローントゥライフ 神様のマリオネット Dorōn to Raifu: Kami-sama no Marionetto?). In the game, the player creates their own playable characters, level objects, and accessories by drawing them using the DS's stylus and Touch Screen. The game was ported to iOS by WayForward Technologies and released by 505 Games on May 22, 2014.[2]

Drawn to Life requires the player to create a hero in order to free a cursed village from an encroaching darkness. It features numerous platforming levels, a top down central village, and other elements such as vehicles, weapons, and platforms, which are drawn or colored by the player using the stylus.

Two sequels have come out, both under the title Drawn to Life: The Next Chapter, for release on the Wii and DS.[5] A spin-off title, Drawn to Life: SpongeBob SquarePants Edition (based on the SpongeBob SquarePants episode "Frankendoodle"), was developed by Altron for the DS.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Drawn to Life-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20070910T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>5th Cell Media</developer>
		<publisher>THQ</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ed, Edd n Eddy - Scam of the Century.nds</path>
		<name>Ed, Edd n Eddy: Scam of the Century</name>
		<desc>In Ed, Edd n Eddy: Scam of the Century, the always-scheming Eds have found their Book O' Scams stolen and in the hands of none other than their enemy Captain Melonhead and the other kids of the cul-de-sac. Now that the Eds' schemes are exposed, the rival kids are dEDD-set on turning the scamming plans against the Eds. All the popular characters, items and locations from the much-loved animated show on Cartoon Network are part of the game, as well as original content for all-new experiences with Ed, Edd and Eddy.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Ed, Edd n Eddy - Scam of the Century-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20071023T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>ART Co., Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>D3 Publisher Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Elebits - The Adventures of Kai and Zero.nds</path>
		<name>Elebits: The Adventures of Kai and Zero</name>
		<desc>Enter into an extraordinary game of hide and seek in this exciting sequel to Elebits! Kai and Zero have been swept off to a magical land and must finish the challenges ahead, to get back home. Seek out the mischievous little Omega Elebits that hold supernatural powers and give you the ability to complete puzzle quests. The more you play the stronger you become as you capture Omega Elebits providing you with incredible magic abilities to solve tasks. Find, capture and befriend the Elebits, raise them and embark on a magical journey using their combined powers to battle through amazing adventures and find a way back home!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Elebits - The Adventures of Kai and Zero-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20090106T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Etrian Odyssey.nds</path>
		<name>Etrian Odyssey</name>
		<desc>In a vast and fertile land lies a small town known as Etria, a peaceful village that became famous for a startling discovery. A crack in the vast forest opened at Etria's edge, leading downward like a gaping maw. It all began there... Your salvation in the labyrinth is in your own hands: Create your own team of adventurers to withstand the maze's fierce battles, while creating your own dungeon maps using the Nintendo DS touch screen outside of combat. Lush 3D graphics and a world-class soundtrack puts an exquisite face on the mortal danger that lurks at every step.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Etrian Odyssey-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20070515T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Atlus Co., Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Atlus Co., Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Etrian Odyssey II - Heroes of Lagaard.nds</path>
		<name>Etrian Odyssey II: Heroes of Lagaard</name>
		<desc>In the Grand Duchy of High Lagaard, it is said that the Duke is descended from inhabitants of a castle in the sky. When an unforeseen crisis befalls the nation, it is decreed that the first explorer to retrieve the Grail of Kings from that mythical floating palace will be rewarded with wealth and fame beyond imagining. Enter the central city of Lagaard and begin your journey to the clouds!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Etrian Odyssey II - Heroes of Lagaard-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20080617T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Atlus Co., Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Atlus Co., Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Etrian Odyssey III - The Drowned City.nds</path>
		<name>Etrian Odyssey III: The Drowned City</name>
		<desc>The embodiment of adventure and discovery in the purest sense, Etrian Odyssey III transports gamers to a sparkling oceanic paradise filled with atmospheric dungeons to chart and survey, vast watery expanses to sail across, and rumors of a sunken city to investigate. Aspiring explorers are responsible for charting their travels utilizing the intuitive touchscreen map editor, meaning that careless cartography could easily spell doom for a fatigued party trying to escape danger. Powerful challenges demand cunning and strategy: players will assemble and fully customize their party of adventurers from a variety of highly specialized classes and sub-classes. For the patient and prepared, fame and fortune await.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Etrian Odyssey III - The Drowned City-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20100921T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Atlus Co., Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Atlus Co., Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Farmtopia.nds</path>
		<name>Farmtopia</name>
		<desc>Put on your overalls and try your hand at running your very own farm. From tending the fields where your cows and sheep graze to gathering eggs for sale at the town market, Farm Frenzy lets you experience all the fun without getting your hands dirty!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Farmtopia-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20101019T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>505 Games</developer>
		<publisher>505 Games</publisher>
		<genre>Life Simulation</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Final Fantasy - The 4 Heroes of Light.nds</path>
		<name>Final Fantasy: The 4 Heroes of Light</name>
		<desc>With Final Fantasy: The 4 Heroes of Light, the Final Fantasy series is rendered anew as an epic storybook adventure by the creators of the Final Fantasy III and Final Fantasy IV Nintendo DS remakes. Players will enter a beautiful fairy-tale world featuring illustrations and character designs by acclaimed character designer Akihiko Yoshida (Final Fantasy III for DS, Final Fantasy XII).</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Final Fantasy - The 4 Heroes of Light-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20101005T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Matrix Software</developer>
		<publisher>Square Enix</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Final Fantasy Crystal Chronicles - Echoes of Time.nds</path>
		<name>Final Fantasy Crystal Chronicles: Echoes of Time</name>
		<desc>An innovative new concept in multiplayer gaming, Final Fantasy Crystal Chronicles: Echoes of Time enables Wii and DS users to play side by side for the first time. This breakthrough in gaming connectivity allows players on both Nintendo platforms to journey together in the fantastical world of the beloved Final Fantasy Crystal Chronicles series. Echoes of Time offers a gameplay system that allows for a seamless, hassle-free in-game switch from single to multiplayer mode. Play anytime, anywhere, with anyone and experience a new level of connectivity with this latest adventure in the FFCC series. A triumphant return from a monster-infested forest marks the completion of the 16-year-old hero's coming-of-age ceremony. However, the hero's joy is short-lived as a young village girl is found to be afflicted by a mysterious illness known as "crystal sickness." Determined to obtain the cure, the hero steps out of the secluded village for the first time, only to discover a world in which crystals are merely artifacts of the past and no longer exist. Players can switch between single and multiplayer modes at any time while playing, enjoying two great gaming options in one integrated experience. A personalized hero can be generated from a choice of the four familiar races of the series; Clavats, Lilties, Selkies or Yukes. Players can continue to enjoy the game even after completing the main adventure, as the New Game+ feature provides increased difficulty and better items with every new round.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Final Fantasy Crystal Chronicles - Echoes of Time-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20090324T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Square Enix</developer>
		<publisher>Square Enix</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Role-Playing</genre>
		<players>4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Final Fantasy Crystal Chronicles - Ring of Fates.nds</path>
		<name>Final Fantasy Crystal Chronicles: Ring of Fates</name>
		<desc>Yuri and Chelinka are fraternal twins who live happily with their father in a small village, but their happiness comes to an abrupt end when an ancient evil force arrives. Now, with his family shattered, Yuri begins to train so that he can be strong enough to fight when the evil returns. Yuri and Chelinka set out on their quest to find their friends, avenge their family, and heal their world.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Final Fantasy Crystal Chronicles - Ring of Fates-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20080311T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Square Enix</developer>
		<publisher>Square Enix</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Role-Playing</genre>
		<players>4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Final Fantasy Fables - Chocobo Tales.nds</path>
		<name>Final Fantasy Fables: Chocobo Tales</name>
		<desc>Final Fantasy Fables: Chocobo Tales starts when the Final Fantasy black magician brings a picture book onto the Chocobo farm. This book is actually home to the great devil Bebuzu, and it sucks the entire farm into its pages! Chocobo heads on an adventure with the white and black magicians in order to stop Bebezu from reviving himself to full form.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Final Fantasy Fables - Chocobo Tales-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20070403T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Square Enix</developer>
		<publisher>Square Enix</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Final Fantasy III.nds</path>
		<name>Final Fantasy III</name>
		<desc>1,000 years ago, the War of the Magi occurred. People remember it as one of the most horrible tragedies in history. Since the War of the Magi, magic has been all but forgotten, technology began to grow, and people returned to seemingly normal lives. The only true worry people had was the Empire, whose leaders were looking to revive the great force once known as "magic".</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Final Fantasy III-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20061115T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Square Enix</developer>
		<publisher>Square Enix</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Final Fantasy IV.nds</path>
		<name>Final Fantasy IV</name>
		<desc>Four elemental Crystals, each possessing awesome power, lie scattered throughout the realm. However, men are quick to covet things which offer strength, and easily corrupted by the might which they possess. Seduced by the promised power of the Crystals, the kingdom of Baron begins employing unprovoked force to seize them from peaceful nations. The dark knight Cecil - Lord Captain of Baron's elite force, the Red Wings - is ordered by his king to obtain the Crystals, but soon begins to question the monarch's motives. Stricken with grief at his own actions, yet burdened by his loyalty to his country and his personal sense of honor, Cecil at last decides to turn from the path of darkness and destruction. Enraged, the king accuses him of disloyalty, strips Cecil of his command, and sends him off to slay a mysterious beast that lurks in the nearby Valley of Mist. Cecil embarks on a fateful journey that will bring trials, betrayals, friendship, loss and self-discovery. Can Cecil open his eyes and become the man of honor that he must be? Dive into the first RPG to incorporate the innovative Active Time Battle system, now further enhanced and refined for the Nintendo DS. Train and customize Whytkin by playing a variety of mini-games and challenge another player to head-to-head battle via local wireless connection.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Final Fantasy IV-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20080721T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Square Enix</developer>
		<publisher>Square Enix</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Final Fantasy Tactics A2 - Grimoire of the Rift.nds</path>
		<name>Final Fantasy Tactics A2: Grimoire of the Rift</name>
		<desc>Embark on a journey through the vibrant world of Ivalice this summer with FINAL FANTASY TACTICS A2: Grimoire of the Rift. As the third entry in the Ivalice Alliance series, this follow-up to the 2003 Game Boy Advance release brings the popular tactical franchise to the Nintendo DS for the first time. FINAL FANTASY TACTICS A2: Grimoire of the Rift will introduce newcomers to an engaging turn-based, grid-oriented battle system as they make new discoveries alongside the hero in this lighthearted adventure.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Final Fantasy Tactics A2 - Grimoire of the Rift-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20080624T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Square Enix</developer>
		<publisher>Square Enix</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing, Strategy</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Final Fantasy XII - Revenant Wings.nds</path>
		<name>Final Fantasy XII: Revenant Wings</name>
		<desc>One year after the events of FINAL FANTASY XII, the young protagonist Vaan travels the skies of Ivalice with his trusted navigator Penelo at his side. Their treasure hunting adventures take them to the sky continent of Lemurés where they meet Llyud, a member of the aegyl race. These mysterious winged people have been living on the floating continent for centuries, but a disturbance has allowed treasure-seeking sky pirates to breach their once-hidden territory. It falls to Vaan and his band of young sky pirates to stand up against the trespassers, and defend this extraordinary world and its people.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Final Fantasy XII - Revenant Wings-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20071120T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Square Enix</developer>
		<publisher>Square Enix</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing, Strategy</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Fire Emblem - Shadow Dragon.nds</path>
		<name>Fire Emblem: Shadow Dragon</name>
		<desc>A reinvention of the original NES titles with revamped graphics and intuitive touch control, Fire Emblem: Shadow Dragon will finally introduce longtime fans to the stories that gave birth to the series nearly 20 years ago in Japan, while introducing the Fire Emblem franchise to a broader audience of strategy and chess fans. Fire Emblem: Shadow Dragon also reveals the back story of Marth, the original lead character in the Fire Emblem series introduced and made popular in North America by the Super Smash Bros. series of fighting games.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Fire Emblem - Shadow Dragon-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20090216T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Intelligent Systems Co., Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing, Strategy</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Frogger - Helmet Chaos.nds</path>
		<name>Frogger: Helmet Chaos</name>
		<desc>In the Frogger's latest adventure, he must stop an evil force that threatens his home, Firefly Swamp, and the nearby kingdom of Bunnington Hollow. To stop Dr. Wani and his destructive mining efforts, you must help Frogger hop and dodge his way to the mastermind's lair. Frogger has unique abilities that allow him to climb walls, double-jump, tongue-grab, and more.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Frogger - Helmet Chaos-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20050927T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami Digital Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Fullmetal Alchemist - Dual Sympathy.nds</path>
		<name>Fullmetal Alchemist: Dual Sympathy</name>
		<desc>Hagane no Renkinjutsushi: Dual Sympathy (Fullmetal Alchemist: Dual Sympathy as it is known in English) is the first in a series of Fullmetal Alchemist games to be released on Nintendo DS. 

A side scrolling action game, Dual Sympathy has the player manipulate alchemy skills using the stylus as you fight enemies, making use of standard attacks and special attacks based on the surrounding environment and items items located in the area.

The story of the game follows the fifty one episode anime series with the same name.

Connectivity bonuses can be unlocked by having the GBA Fullmetal Alchemist games in the GBA slot of the DS.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Fullmetal Alchemist - Dual Sympathy-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20061212T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Natsume</developer>
		<publisher>Destineer</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Golden Sun - Dark Dawn.nds</path>
		<name>Golden Sun: Dark Dawn</name>
		<desc>After going dark six years ago, 2010 will see a new dawn. Golden Sun DS updates the popular portable Golden Sun role-playing series with an impressive graphical style. This installment follows the story of the previous heroes' descendants and immerses players into the magic of its adventure by pushing the boundaries of intuitive touch-screen controls.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Golden Sun - Dark Dawn-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20101129T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Camelot Software Planning</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Hamsterz Life.nds</path>
		<name>Hamsterz Life</name>
		<desc>Hamsterz Life is a hamster simulation video game released by Ubisoft for the Nintendo DS. Hamsterz Life is also known as Love ? Hamster or Love Love Hamster in Japan.


Gameplay[edit]
Hamsterz Life is from the Petz series from Ubisoft for the handheld systems. Being released after Petz 5, it is part of the second Petz series. Hamsterz Life lets you raise several breeds of hamsters and build fully customizable homes for them to live in. Just as in the other Petz games, players can interact with their hamsters by training, playing with, and feeding them.

At the start of the game, players can select their first hamster and name it. The hamster will then appear in a cage and be ready to play. Various actions can be chosen including training, feeding, care and other options. Training consists of teaching the hamster words (which they repeat back in their own hamster speak) by speaking the set phrases into the DS microphone. The hamster can repeat these phrases back, but inaudibly. Players can clean the cage and brush their hamsters. Hamsterz Life also includes many mini-games to play. Players can only have one hamster at home at once, any other hamsters that are owned are left with a girl with hamster ears until you wish to switch. Your hamsters can visit with the hamsters of friends who also own Hamsterz Life. When playing mini-games, if you win you receive prizes such as food or toys. You can also let your hamster out of its cage to play in the surrounding room. There are present boxes in the room, which contain prizes you receive when your hamster finds them.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Hamsterz Life-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20061128T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>MTO</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Life Simulation</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Harvest Moon DS.nds</path>
		<name>Harvest Moon DS</name>
		<desc>Harvest Moon DS is a farm simulation role-playing video game for the Nintendo DS, part of the Story of Seasons series. It was published and developed by Marvelous Interactive Inc., and released in Japan on March 17, 2005. It is the first entry in the series without series creator Yasuhiro Wada heavily involved, though it borrows many assets from Harvest Moon: Friends of Mineral Town and Harvest Moon: A Wonderful Life, such as the graphical style from the former and setting of the latter.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Harvest Moon DS-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20060912T000000</releasedate>
		<genre>Life Simulation</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Harvest Moon DS - Grand Bazaar.nds</path>
		<name>Harvest Moon DS: Grand Bazaar</name>
		<desc>Harvest Moon DS: Grand Bazaar is a video game released on December 18, 2008 by Marvelous Interactive in Japan, and released on August 24, 2010 by Natsume in North America. It was also released in Europe on September 30, 2011 by Rising Star Games. The game is the nineteenth game in the Story of Seasons series and the fifth game in the series for the Nintendo DS.

In this Harvest Moon title, players are tasked with returning Zephyr Town's bazaar back to its former glory, as well as growing crops, raising animals, and romancing some of the villagers.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Harvest Moon DS - Grand Bazaar-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20100824T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Marvelous Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Natsume</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Harvest Moon DS - Island of Happiness.nds</path>
		<name>Harvest Moon DS: Island of Happiness</name>
		<desc>In Harvest Moon: Island of Happiness you develop the island by growing crops and taking care of animals and expanding your farm. The better you do, the more the island will grow, and the more others will start to move onto the island. Though it was not your original dream, now is you chance to create your very own paradise!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Harvest Moon DS - Island of Happiness-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20080826T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tose</developer>
		<publisher>Marvelous</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy, Life Simulation</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Harvest Moon DS - Sunshine Islands.nds</path>
		<name>Harvest Moon DS: Sunshine Islands</name>
		<desc>The islands are in peril! Years ago, a powerful earthquake struck the Sunshine Islands. In Harvest Moon: Sunshine Islands, it's up to the player to raise the sunken islands by finding the magical Sun Stones. Raise the islands to meet new characters, harvest new crops, and befriend animals such as ducks, monkeys, and badgers. In Harvest Moon: Sunshine Islands, players rejoin all of the beloved characters from Harvest Moon: Island of Happiness, and get to meet a number of new friends as well. Players will grow and harvest crops, care for animals, mine, fish, and compete in festivals in their quest to restore the Sunshine Islands to their former glory. With a little luck, they may even find true love and start a family along the way.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Harvest Moon DS - Sunshine Islands-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20091112T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Marvelous Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Natsume</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Harvest Moon DS - The Tale of Two Towns.nds</path>
		<name>Harvest Moon DS: The Tale of Two Towns</name>
		<desc>Harvest Moon: Tale of Two Towns is a Life Simulation Role-playing Game (RPG) for Nintendo DS. The game features classic Life Sim gameplay involving farming, the raising and care of animals and eventual marriage. Additional features include an all-new storyline involving the player in an ongoing rivalry between two towns, the ability to play as either a boy or a girl, an in-game quest bulletin board system, wireless functionality allowing you to visit friends in-game fields, new in-game activities and more.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Harvest Moon DS - The Tale of Two Towns-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20110920T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Marvelous Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Natsume</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing, Life Simulation, Sandbox</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Harvest Moon DS Cute.nds</path>
		<name>Harvest Moon DS Cute</name>
		<desc>Harvest Moon DS Cute (牧場物語コロボックルステーションforガール bokujō monogatari korobokkuru sutēshon for gāru?) is the female version of Harvest Moon DS for the Nintendo DS. It was published and developed by Marvelous Interactive Inc., and first released in Japan on December 8, 2005. Harvest Moon DS Cute replaces the male protagonist from Harvest Moon DS with a female character; players may choose either Pony from Harvest Moon: Another Wonderful Life or Claire from Harvest Moon: More Friends of Mineral Town. The Japanese version introduced a system not present in the North American version known as the "Best Friend" system. This allowed the player to essentially marry any of the bachelorettes from Harvest Moon DS, as well as the bachelors.

 
The plot of Harvest Moon DS Cute is different than that of Harvest Moon DS. In this version of the game, the player's mother sends a wish to the Harvest Goddess that you may be a successful farmer. The Harvest Goddess eventually determines the player has no work ethic, and tells the Harvest King what she thinks. The Harvest King angrily tells the Harvest Goddess she isn't trying hard enough, and she is slacking off in her old age. The Harvest Goddess then calls the Harvest King a "big baldy", and is turned into stone. The Harvest Sprites defend the Harvest Goddess, which angers the Harvest King even more, and he sends the Harvest Sprites and the Harvest Goddess to another world as punishment. He then</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Harvest Moon DS Cute-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20080328T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Marvelous Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Natsume</publisher>
		<genre>Life Simulation</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Jackass - The Game DS.nds</path>
		<name>Jackass - The Game Ds</name>
		<desc>Johnny Knoxville and the jackass crew are knee deep in their latest series of ill-conceived stunts, pranks and acts of indecency, and this time you're in the director's seat. Take control of your favorite degenerates through a massive range of all-new challenges. An onslaught of absurd situations lower the bar and up the ante for the self-inflicted injury, degradation and low moral caliber you've come to love and expect from this special group of idiots.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Jackass - The Game DS-image.png</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20080115T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Red Mile Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Sidhe Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Kingdom Hearts - 358-2 Days.nds</path>
		<name>Kingdom Hearts 358/2 Days</name>
		<desc>Kingdom Hearts 358/2 Days revolves around Roxas, the "other" hero from
Kingdom Hearts II. Players follow Roxas through his days among Organization XIII's ranks, unraveling the events that took place during the year that Sora was asleep, and ultimately revealing one of the Kingdom Hearts saga's most shocking secrets. Players and their friends will join Roxas, his friend Axel and the mysterious fourteenth member of Organization XIII on a journey across charming, vibrant worlds full of Square Enix's and Disney's beloved characters.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Kingdom Hearts - 358-2 Days-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20090929T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hand</developer>
		<publisher>Squaresoft</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Role-Playing</genre>
		<players>4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Kingdom Hearts - Re-coded.nds</path>
		<name>Kingdom Hearts Re:Coded</name>
		<desc>Sora's journey in Kingdom Hearts II has drawn to a close, and now a new tale is set to begin.Jiminy Cricket is looking over the journal he used to document his first adventure with Sora when he discovers a mysterious message. He didn't write it - so how on earth did it get there? King Mickey is determined to find out, so he and his friends decide to digitize the journal and delve into its deepest secrets. Inside this "datascape" dwells a second Sora who is about to embark on a grand adventure of his very own.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Kingdom Hearts - Re-coded-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20101007T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Square Enix</developer>
		<publisher>Square Enix</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Kirby - Canvas Curse.nds</path>
		<name>Kirby: Canvas Curse</name>
		<desc>Your DS stylus has been infused with the power to paint! When Kirby gets turned into a ball by an evil witch, your hand-drawn rainbow paths become the only way he can find power-ups and reach the gates of each world. Draw loops to make him speed up, make ramps to jump danger, and draw walls to block laser beams and cannon blasts as you explore seven worlds packed with adventure! Get in touch: Stun enemies, break blocks, and much more - all with a touch of the stylus! Be a copycat: Tap Kirby to dash into enemies and copy their abilities. Eleven abilities in all! So many modes: Try timed challenges, take on bosses, or play simple but fun mini-games!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Kirby - Canvas Curse-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20050613T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>HAL Laboratory</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Kirby - Squeak Squad.nds</path>
		<name>Kirby: Squeak Squad</name>
		<desc>Kirby: Squeak Squad, known in Europe as Kirby: Mouse Attack and in Japan as Kirby of the Stars: Calling on the Dorotche Gang (Japanese: 星のカービィ 参上! ドロッチェ団 Hepburn: Hoshi no Kābī Sanjō! Dorocche Dan?), is a 2006-07 platforming video game developed by HAL Laboratory, Flagship and Natsume (the latter as seen in the end credits) and published by Nintendo for the Nintendo DS handheld video game console. Unlike the previous Nintendo DS title, Kirby: Canvas Curse, Squeak Squad is a traditional platformer which uses the face buttons instead of the touch screen to control Kirby.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Kirby - Squeak Squad-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20061204T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>HAL Laboratory</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure, Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Kirby Mass Attack.nds</path>
		<name>Kirby: Mass Attack</name>
		<desc>One day, an evildoer with a magic cane appears and splits Kirby into 10 pieces. Kirby sets off on a journey to return to his original form. Players use the touch screen to control a mass of Kirby characters in a new and novel way. Swipe the touch screen to launch them in a mass attack against enemies, then tap the enemies into submission.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Kirby Mass Attack-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20110919T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>HAL Laboratory</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Kirby Super Star Ultra.nds</path>
		<name>Kirby: Super Star Ultra</name>
		<desc>Kirby Super Star Ultra for the Nintendo DS re-imagines one of the most beloved Kirby games of all time. The game features new graphics and fully rendered animated cut scenes. With so many adventures waiting to be unlocked, there will never be a dull moment as Kirby runs, floats, copies enemies and uses Helpers to fight King Dedede and Meta Knight. New modes like Revenge of the King and Meta Knight Ultra await, along with classics like The Great Cave Offensive and Milky Way Wishes. On top of the main modes, there are also three new touch-screen-controlled mini-games that can be played with up to three friends via DS Download Play. Not only that, but players can go on Kirby adventures with a friend via local wireless as well.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Kirby Super Star Ultra-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20080922T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Platform</genre>
		<players>4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./LEGO Star Wars - The Complete Saga.nds</path>
		<name>LEGO Star Wars: The Complete Saga</name>
		<desc>Lego Star Wars: The Complete Saga is a video game based on the Star Wars-themed toy line by the Lego Group. It is a combination of the game Lego Star Wars: The Video Game and its sequel Lego Star Wars II: The Original Trilogy, which includes all episodes, one through six. The game was announced by LucasArts on May 25, 2007 at Celebration IV and was released for the Xbox 360, PlayStation 3, Wii, and Nintendo DS on November 6, 2007 in North America. The compilation title was released for the PC on October 13, 2009 in the US.[11] Its sequel, Lego Star Wars III: The Clone Wars, was released in March, 2011. The Mac OS X version of the game was released on November 12, 2010 by Feral Interactive.,[2] iOS version of the game was released on December 12, 2013, and the Android version was released on January 1, 2015.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/LEGO Star Wars - The Complete Saga-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20071106T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>TT Fusion</developer>
		<publisher>LucasArts Entertainment Company LLC</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Line Rider 2 - Unbound.nds</path>
		<name>Line Rider 2: Unbound</name>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Line Rider 2 - Unbound-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20080812T000000</releasedate>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Lunar - Dragon Song.nds</path>
		<name>Lunar: Dragon Song</name>
		<desc>Through the Darkness find the Light!
When The Legends of Dragons were first born, an age of darkness descended on the world of Lunar. Join the untried hero Jian and his friends on their journey to save Lunar from the powerful forces of evil.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Lunar - Dragon Song-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20050927T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Game Arts</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Magical Starsign.nds</path>
		<name>Magical Starsign</name>
		<desc>The students of Will O'Wisp magical academy have a little problem: Their teacher has mysteriously disappeared. After commandeering a handful of rockets to rescue her, they've wound up on a strange (and sometimes scary) adventure through outer space. Now players must rescue both their classmates AND their teacher - and just maybe the whole solar system while they're at it. Explore strange planets. Players see the sights of this strange, sci-fi fantasy setting as they uncover the secret behind their teacher's disappearance in this epic role-playing game. The stylus controls everything, from combat to conversations to outfitting allies. Simple controls make it easy to play but a challenge to master. Players can link up wirelessly with five friends and explore the amigo dungeon together - they'll find unending challenges and incredible rewards as they delve into the depths of this unique multiplayer experience.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Magical Starsign-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20061023T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Brownie Brown</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
		<players>4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mario &amp; Luigi - Bowser's Inside Story.nds</path>
		<name>Mario &amp; Luigi: Bowser's Inside Story</name>
		<desc>Mario &amp; Luigi: Bowser's Inside Story is the third game in the Mario &amp; Luigi series of games. Players control Mario and Luigi simultaneously in the side-scrolling platform environment of Bowser's body, while also controlling the Koopa King himself in the top-down world of the Mushroom Kingdom. Similar to games like Earthbound, enemy encounters are seen as actual enemies that players can avoid or attempt to strike early. The actual battles are a combination of turn-based menu attacks, and timed reactions to enemies during battle. By watching the way an enemy reacts, you can anticipate their attack and avoid it or counterattack.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Mario &amp; Luigi - Bowser's Inside Story-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20090914T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>AlphaDream</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mario &amp; Luigi - Partners in Time.nds</path>
		<name>Mario &amp; Luigi: Partners in Time</name>
		<desc>The famous Mario Brothers return in this sequel to the humorous Superstar Saga. In this adventure, Princess Peach takes a trip in a time machine, but when it returns, there's only a monster inside! The heroic brothers travel back in time only to discover that evil alien life forms known as the Shroobs have taken over the Mushroom Kingdom, and no-one is safe! They soon meet up with their younger selves, and set out to stop the alien menace, not to mention rescue the Princess!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Mario &amp; Luigi - Partners in Time-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20051128T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>AlphaDream</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mario vs. Donkey Kong - Mini-Land Mayhem!.nds</path>
		<name>Mario vs. Donkey Kong: Mini-Land Mayhem</name>
		<desc>At the grand opening of Mario's third theme park, the first 100 guests receive a new Mini Pauline toy. Donkey Kong arrives as the 101st guest and finds himself out of luck. He grabs Pauline and heads into the park with Mario and his Mini Marios in hot pursuit. The fourth game in the series adds new challenges and new opportunities for users to share what they have created.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Mario vs. Donkey Kong - Mini-Land Mayhem!-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20101114T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mario vs. Donkey Kong 2 - March of the Minis.nds</path>
		<name>Mario vs. Donkey Kong 2: March of the Minis</name>
		<desc>Mario vs. Donkey Kong 2: March of the Minis is an action/puzzle game where the object is to bring as many Mini-Marios to the exit door as possible by solving the puzzle. All the puzzles are fairly small and take up anywhere from one screen to four screens (2x2) in size. All the Mini-Marios that are collected in each room are then used in the Donkey Kong boss battle at the end of the world. All of the control is done with the stylus; no buttons are used at all.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Mario vs. Donkey Kong 2 - March of the Minis-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20060925T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./MegaMan Battle Network 5 - Double Team DS.nds</path>
		<name>Mega Man Battle Network 5: Double Team DS</name>
		<desc>Mega Man Battle Network 5: Double Team is a dual screen version of the Game Boy Advance title. The DS will combine both Team Protoman and Team Colonel in one game, but add specific content unique to the Nintendo DS version. The second screen comes into play by giving players direct access to their Cyber Map and PET. The microphone can be "yelled" into to power up Mega Man during battle. And using the Nintendo DS's GBA slot, players can carry over battle chips earned in past Mega Man Battle Network games for use in the Nintendo DS edition.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/MegaMan Battle Network 5 - Double Team DS-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20051101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./MegaMan Star Force - Dragon.nds</path>
		<name>Mega Man Star Force: Dragon</name>
		<desc>Mega Man Star Force is the successor to the Megaman Battle Network series. You take control of Geo Stelar, who partners with an EM-being known as Omega-Xis. Geo uses Omega's power to become Mega Man, and defends the world from the FM-ians.

Geo Stelar, an introvert who lost his dad to a space mission, bumps into EM-being Omega-Xis (aka Mega). When Mega claims to have information of Geo's father, Geo decides to work with him. Partnering up in a "EM Wave Change", Geo gains amazing power, and takes it upon himself to stop Planet FM from invading Earth, calling himself Mega Man in order to protect his identity.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/MegaMan Star Force - Dragon-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20070807T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Role-Playing</genre>
		<players>6</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./MegaMan Star Force - Leo.nds</path>
		<name>Mega Man Star Force: Leo</name>
		<desc>Mega Man Star Force introduces a new lead character, a boy named Subaru Hoshikawa, who puts on special "visualizer" goggles left to him by his father, triggering a specific wave and summoning the presence of a mysterious alien life form named Warlock. Dangerous creatures from Warlock's planet have come to attack Earth, so they must join together to transform into Mega Man in order to defeat these menacing forces. Specific to the Leo version - turning up the heat, Fire Leo uses a special Flame Burner attack that can incinerate enemies in its path.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/MegaMan Star Force - Leo-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20070807T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./MegaMan Star Force - Pegasus.nds</path>
		<name>Mega Man Star Force: Pegasus</name>
		<desc>A spin-off of the Mega Man Battle Network franchise, this game brings the franchise back with similar RPG gameplay but with an all-new Mega Man character and storyline to play through. This action RPG blends exploration with fast-paced battles, as players travel between real world and virtual "Wave World."

In Mega Man Star Force, players explore towns and interact with people in the real world while the action-packed battles take place in the virtual "Wave World." Enemy encounters take place on a three by five grid in a 3D perspective, where players use a portfolio of Battle Cards that each have distinct attributes and attack powers. As the story progresses, players will acquire additional cards to build an arsenal that reflects their personal strategy. Players can also connect wirelessly via the Nintendo Wi-Fi connection with friends to create a Brother Band network, where they can share cards and get status upgrades.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/MegaMan Star Force - Pegasus-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20070807T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom Production Studio 2</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./MegaMan Star Force 2 - Zerker x Ninja.nds</path>
		<name>Mega Man Star Force 2: Zerker x Ninja</name>
		<desc>Mega Man Star Force 2 blends a unique formula of RPG exploration elements with fast-paced action, as players travel and battle between coexisting worlds, the physical world and the virtual Wave World, to unravel the mystery around this new troublemaker.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/MegaMan Star Force 2 - Zerker x Ninja-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20080624T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure, Strategy</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./MegaMan Star Force 2 - Zerker x Saurian.nds</path>
		<name>Mega Man Star Force 2: Zerker x Saurian</name>
		<desc>Mega Man Star Force 2 blends a unique formula of RPG exploration elements with fast-paced action, as players travel and battle between coexisting worlds, the physical world and the virtual Wave World, to unravel the mystery around this new troublemaker.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/MegaMan Star Force 2 - Zerker x Saurian-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20080624T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure, Strategy</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Megaman Star Force 3 - Black Ace.nds</path>
		<name>Mega Man Star Force 3: Black Ace</name>
		<desc>Mega Man Star Force returns in the most thrilling series adventure yet, delivering totally upgraded and cutting-edge online communication and device customization technologies through a portable RPG adventure that is brought to life in the iconic, action-driven Mega Man way! New to the series are "Noise Changes," random enhancements that change Mega Man's form and unlock new abilities. There are more than 100 transformations possible. Mega Man Star Force 3 will be available in two versions, Red Joker and Black Ace, each with their own unique Noise Types. Mega Man Star Force 3 blends a unique formula of RPG exploration elements with fast-paced action, as players travel and battle between coexisting worlds, the physical world and the virtual Wave World. Players will encounter enemies in the virtual Wave World and battle them on three-by-five battle grids with their Battle Card deck. Mega Man Star Force 3 also adds a new feature called "Rezon," which allow players to fill in profiles about battles and their team name/symbol.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Megaman Star Force 3 - Black Ace-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20090630T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure, Strategy</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Megaman Star Force 3 - Red Joker.nds</path>
		<name>Mega Man Star Force 3: Red Joker</name>
		<desc>Mega Man Star Force returns in the most thrilling series adventure yet, delivering totally upgraded and cutting-edge online communication and device customization technologies through a portable RPG adventure that is brought to life in the iconic, action-driven Mega Man way! New to the series are "Noise Changes," random enhancements that change Mega Man's form and unlock new abilities. There are more than 100 transformations possible. Mega Man Star Force 3 will be available in two versions, Red Joker and Black Ace, each with their own unique Noise Types. Mega Man Star Force 3 blends a unique formula of RPG exploration elements with fast-paced action, as players travel and battle between coexisting worlds, the physical world and the virtual Wave World. Players will encounter enemies in the virtual Wave World and battle them on three-by-five battle grids with their Battle Card deck. Mega Man Star Force 3 also adds a new feature called "Rezon," which allow players to fill in profiles about battles and their team name/symbol.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Megaman Star Force 3 - Red Joker-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20090630T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure, Strategy</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./MegaMan Zero Collection.nds</path>
		<name>Mega Man Zero Collection</name>
		<desc>The first Mega Man ZERO game was released in 2002. It featured Zero, a popular Capcom character that was introduced in the Mega Man X series. The Mega Man ZERO series follows Zero through a dark and thrilling 2D action-adventure with high-quality visuals and action. Users can expect to make use of Zero's trademarks weapons like the Z-sabor and Buster Shot. There will also be interesting devices like the Chain Rod and Zero Knuckle. For the first time, the Mega Man ZERO series will be available for Nintendo DS, complete with all-new modes.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/MegaMan Zero Collection-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20100608T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Inti Creates</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure, Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./MegaMan ZX.nds</path>
		<name>Mahjong 300</name>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/MegaMan ZX-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20110916T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>cerasus.media GmbH</developer>
		<publisher>Avanquest</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./MegaMan ZX Advent.nds</path>
		<name>Mega Man ZX Advent</name>
		<desc>In Mega Man ZX Advent, the main characters discover the power of the mysterious "Biometal model A," which on its own has several attacks, but also has a special Megamerge ability which allows the character to transform into one of eight "Pseudoroid" bosses that each have a unique set of abilities. Once a boss is defeated, players can emulate their powers to find hidden routes, discover rare items and aid their battles against more powerful enemies. The title takes full advantage of the Nintendo DS features to enhance the action-packed gameplay and story line of the popular series.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/MegaMan ZX Advent-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20071023T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Platform</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Monster Rancher DS.nds</path>
		<name>Monster Rancher DS</name>
		<desc>Raise, Train and Battle your monsters in Monster Rancher DS, the newest addition to the beloved breeding series. Filled with nostalgia from past games, fans of the series will recognize popular characters and monsters such as Mocchi and Suezo, in addition to new monsters to discover. Generate monsters by drawing pictures in the "magic Field," or by speaking into the microphone in "Incantation" mode. Use your best strategy to raise, train, and battle your monsters. Can you become a legendary master breeder?</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Monster Rancher DS-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20100803T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>CING, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>UFO Interactive Games, Inc.</publisher>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./MySims.nds</path>
		<name>MySims</name>
		<desc>Explore a whole new world with MySims - it's your world to transform. Move to a town that has been struggling lately. With a little creativity and some help from the locals, you can make this place thrive. Improve the town to attract new characters, from the Italian Chef and Florist to the Kickboxing Instructor and DJ. Discover what the residents want and need, so that you can help them enjoy life in their town.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/MySims-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20070918T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>EA Redwood Shores</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./MySims - Racing.nds</path>
		<name>MySims Racing</name>
		<desc>Race into an all-new adventure with MySims Racing! Test your reflexes, strategy and skill by tricking out cars, completing challenges, and winning championships. Speed up any get-together with 4-player mode. Pick cool race-themed outfits and accessories for your MySim, save Speedville, and come race with us!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/MySims - Racing-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20090608T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Artificial Mind &amp; Movement</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Racing, Sandbox</genre>
		<players>4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mystery Dungeon - Shiren the Wanderer.nds</path>
		<name>Mystery Dungeon: Shiren the Wanderer</name>
		<desc>Shiren and Koppa still have their primary objective of finding the Lair of the Golden Condor but an adventure is not complete without visiting new towns and going on exciting side quests! Check out some of side quests they go on and the towns these two warriors visit along the way!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Mystery Dungeon - Shiren the Wanderer-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20080304T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Chunsoft</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./New Super Mario Bros..nds</path>
		<name>New Super Mario Bros.</name>
		<desc>In an all new 2D side-scrolling adventure, Mario and Luigi return after nearly fifteen years. The first traditional Mario Bros. game since Super Mario World.

The character models are rendered in real time 3D, allowing for a far greater number of moves ever before seen in a Mario Bros. title. Also as the game is on DS, the touch screen allows players to store an additional power-up and view the distance still to go in a level.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/New Super Mario Bros.-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20060515T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Platform</genre>
		<players>4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Nicktoons - Attack of the Toybots.nds</path>
		<name>Nicktoons: Attack of the Toybots</name>
		<desc>The evil Professor Calamitous is at it again, but this time he’s gone too far. He has created evil robots that look just like our Nicktoons heroes. Now, SpongeBob, Jimmy Neutron, Danny Phantom, Timmy Turner, and Tak must stop them and the Professor no matter what it takes. By using new attacks, and awesome mech suits, now you can help our heroes stop the evil professor before he wreaks havoc everywhere.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Nicktoons - Attack of the Toybots-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20071023T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Natsume</developer>
		<publisher>THQ</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Nicktoons - Battle for Volcano Island.nds</path>
		<name>Nicktoons: Battle for Volcano Island</name>
		<desc>Join SpongeBob, Timmy Tuner, and Danny Phantom in an all out battle to stop the evil Mawgu from taking control of Volcano Island!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Nicktoons - Battle for Volcano Island-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20061024T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Natsume</developer>
		<publisher>THQ</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Nicktoons Unite!.nds</path>
		<name>Nicktoons Unite!</name>
		<desc>For the first time ever the greatest Nicktoons villains face off against your favorite characters including SpongeBob SquarePants, Timmy Turner, Jimmy Neutron, and Danny Phantom. Combine their powers to take out the Evil Syndicate, along with the devastating Doomsday device! It’s good vs. evil where only one set of Nicktoons will prevail!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Nicktoons Unite!-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20060203T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Climax Studios</developer>
		<publisher>THQ</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Nintendo DS Browser.nds</path>
		<name>Nintendo DS Browser</name>
		<desc>The Nintendo DS Browser is a version of the Opera web browser for use on the Nintendo DS, developed by Opera Software and Nintendo. The Nintendo DS Browser comes in separate versions for the Nintendo DS and the Nintendo DS Lite, this is due to differing physical size requirements for the memory expansion cartridge included with the browser. The Nintendo DSi is incompatible with the Nintendo DS Browser, though a DSi compatible version of Opera 9.5, Nintendo DSi Browser (ニンテンドーDSiブラウザー Nintendō Dī Esu Ai Burauzā), was available free from the DSi Shop, but after the Nintendo DSi Shop closed on March 31, 2017, the Nintendo DSi Browser was no longer available for download. </desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Nintendo DS Browser-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20060724T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo, Opera Soft</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Sandbox</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Nintendogs - Chihuahua &amp; Friends.nds</path>
		<name>Nintendogs: Chihuahua &amp; Friends</name>
		<desc>Nintendogs (Japanese: ニンテンドッグス Hepburn: Nintendoggusu?) is a realtime pet simulation video game developed and published by Nintendo for the Nintendo DS handheld video game console. It was first released in Japan, and was later released in North America, Australia, Europe, and other regions. It was originally released in three different versions: Dachshund &amp; Friends, Lab &amp; Friends (Shiba &amp; Friends in Japan), and Chihuahua &amp; Friends. It has been re-released twice since then, first as a bundled release with a special edition Nintendo DS with a new version called Nintendogs: Best Friends, and then later as Nintendogs: Dalmatian &amp; Friends.

Nintendogs uses the DS's touchscreen and built-in microphone. The touch screen allows the player to pet a dog, as well as to use various items that can be found or purchased. These range from balls and frisbees, to toys, to grooming supplies to keep the dogs happy. The microphone is used to call to the player's dog by speaking the name given to the dog in the beginning of the game as well as to teach the dog tricks such as "sit" or "roll over". Players can bring their dogs on walks and to the park if they so choose. They may interact with other players in multi-player by using the DS's wireless linkup. It also uses the DS's internal clock and calendar to allow the dog to grow hungrier or dirtier based on the elapsed time.

Nintendogs received critical acclaim. It has an aggregate score of 85% at Game Rankings,[3] and has won many awards, including the 2006 Innovation Award from PC World and Best Handheld Game from the Associated Press. As of March 31, 2015, all versions of Nintendogs combined have sold 23.96 million copies worldwide, making it second on the Nintendo DS best-sellers list, behind only New Super Mario Bros.[4] Because of Nintendogs' success, Nintendo has made several related products, including Nintendogs toys[5] and a series of Nintendogs trading cards.[6] At E3 2010, it was announced a sequel, titled Nintendogs + Cats, would be released for the Nintendo 3DS.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Nintendogs - Chihuahua &amp; Friends-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20050822T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Life Simulation</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Nintendogs - Lab &amp; Friends.nds</path>
		<name>Nintendogs: Lab &amp; Friends</name>
		<desc>Nintendogs (Japanese: ニンテンドッグス Hepburn: Nintendoggusu?) is a realtime pet simulation video game developed and published by Nintendo for the Nintendo DS handheld video game console. It was first released in Japan, and was later released in North America, Australia, Europe, and other regions. It was originally released in three different versions: Dachshund &amp; Friends, Lab &amp; Friends (Shiba &amp; Friends in Japan), and Chihuahua &amp; Friends. It has been re-released twice since then, first as a bundled release with a special edition Nintendo DS with a new version called Nintendogs: Best Friends, and then later as Nintendogs: Dalmatian &amp; Friends.

Nintendogs uses the DS's touchscreen and built-in microphone. The touch screen allows the player to pet a dog, as well as to use various items that can be found or purchased. These range from balls and frisbees, to toys, to grooming supplies to keep the dogs happy. The microphone is used to call to the player's dog by speaking the name given to the dog in the beginning of the game as well as to teach the dog tricks such as "sit" or "roll over". Players can bring their dogs on walks and to the park if they so choose. They may interact with other players in multi-player by using the DS's wireless linkup. It also uses the DS's internal clock and calendar to allow the dog to grow hungrier or dirtier based on the elapsed time.

Nintendogs received critical acclaim. It has an aggregate score of 85% at Game Rankings,[3] and has won many awards, including the 2006 Innovation Award from PC World and Best Handheld Game from the Associated Press. As of March 31, 2015, all versions of Nintendogs combined have sold 23.96 million copies worldwide, making it second on the Nintendo DS best-sellers list, behind only New Super Mario Bros.[4] Because of Nintendogs' success, Nintendo has made several related products, including Nintendogs toys[5] and a series of Nintendogs trading cards.[6] At E3 2010, it was announced a sequel, titled Nintendogs + Cats, would be released for the Nintendo 3DS.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Nintendogs - Lab &amp; Friends-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20050822T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo EAD Group No. 1</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Life Simulation</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ontamarama.nds</path>
		<name>Ontamarama</name>
		<desc>Ontamarama (おんたま♪おんぷ島へん Ontama Onputouhen) is a rhythm game published by Atlus for the Nintendo DS. It was released in Japan in July 2007, and in North America on November 6, 2007. The game uses both of the DS's screens, touch functionality, and the microphone during game play.[1] The story revolves around colorful spirits called Ontama, who live on a tropical island and can create music. The player must quickly capture Ontama with the stylus while keeping up with the beat.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Ontamarama-image.png</image>
		<releasedate>20071106T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Noise Factory</developer>
		<publisher>Atlus Co., Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Music</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pokemon - Black Version.nds</path>
		<name>Pokémon Black Version</name>
		<desc>Pokémon Black Version and Pokémon White Version feature new Pokémon that players can catch, train and battle as they progress through the game, and some Pokémon can only be caught in one version of the game. For example, the Legendary Pokémon Reshiram can only be caught in Pokémon Black Version, while the Legendary Pokémon Zekrom can only be caught in Pokémon White Version. Additionally, the two games feature different areas for the first time in the series, with the game world of Pokémon Black Version featuring a unique metropolitan area called Black City, and a lush, green area named White Forest only found in Pokémon White Version. Pokémon Black Version and Pokémon White Version also mark the first time in a Pokémon video game that the seasons will change in the game world. Certain Pokémon appear more frequently during different seasons, and players can only access some areas during a specific season.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Pokemon - Black Version-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20110306T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Game Freak</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure, Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pokemon - Black Version 2.nds</path>
		<name>Pokémon Black Version</name>
		<desc>Pokémon Black Version and Pokémon White Version feature new Pokémon that players can catch, train and battle as they progress through the game, and some Pokémon can only be caught in one version of the game. For example, the Legendary Pokémon Reshiram can only be caught in Pokémon Black Version, while the Legendary Pokémon Zekrom can only be caught in Pokémon White Version. Additionally, the two games feature different areas for the first time in the series, with the game world of Pokémon Black Version featuring a unique metropolitan area called Black City, and a lush, green area named White Forest only found in Pokémon White Version. Pokémon Black Version and Pokémon White Version also mark the first time in a Pokémon video game that the seasons will change in the game world. Certain Pokémon appear more frequently during different seasons, and players can only access some areas during a specific season.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Pokemon - Black Version 2-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20110306T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Game Freak</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure, Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pokemon - Platinum Version.nds</path>
		<name>Pokémon Platinum Version</name>
		<desc>Another world has emerged in the Sinnoh Region...

...A world where space &amp; time are altered!

New Discoveries, New Challenges!
Catch, train, and battle your favorite Pokémon, and discover ancient, mythical Pokémon in this exciting new adventure!

Expanded Online Options!
New experiences in the Wi-Fi Plaza and Battle Frontier!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Pokemon - Platinum Version-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20080913T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Game Freak</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure, Role-Playing</genre>
		<players>4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pokemon - White Version.nds</path>
		<name>Pokémon White Version</name>
		<desc>Pokemon Black Version and Pokemon White Version feature new Pokemon that players can catch, train and battle as they progress through the game, and some Pokemon can only be caught in one version of the game. For example, the Legendary Pokemon Reshiram can only be caught in Pokemon Black Version, while the Legendary Pokemon Zekrom can only be caught in Pokemon White Version. Additionally, the two games feature different areas for the first time in the series, with the game world of Pokemon Black Version featuring a unique metropolitan area called Black City, and a lush, green area named White Forest only found in Pokemon White Version. Pokemon Black Version and Pokemon White Version also mark the first time in a Pokemon video game that the seasons will change in the game world. Certain Pokemon appear more frequently during different seasons, and players can only access some areas during a specific season.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Pokemon - White Version-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20110306T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Game Freak</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
		<players>4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pokemon - White Version 2.nds</path>
		<name>Pokémon White Version</name>
		<desc>Pokemon Black Version and Pokemon White Version feature new Pokemon that players can catch, train and battle as they progress through the game, and some Pokemon can only be caught in one version of the game. For example, the Legendary Pokemon Reshiram can only be caught in Pokemon Black Version, while the Legendary Pokemon Zekrom can only be caught in Pokemon White Version. Additionally, the two games feature different areas for the first time in the series, with the game world of Pokemon Black Version featuring a unique metropolitan area called Black City, and a lush, green area named White Forest only found in Pokemon White Version. Pokemon Black Version and Pokemon White Version also mark the first time in a Pokemon video game that the seasons will change in the game world. Certain Pokemon appear more frequently during different seasons, and players can only access some areas during a specific season.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Pokemon - White Version 2-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20110306T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Game Freak</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
		<players>4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pokemon Diamond.nds</path>
		<name>Pokémon Diamond Version</name>
		<desc>Pokémon Diamond Version introduce Trainers to a different land and many Pokémon to catch! Explore the lakes, forests, and mountains of the Sinnoh region, seeking out Pokémon such as the Bug-type Kricketot or the hard-headed Rock- and Steel-type Shieldon. And if you're lucky, you might bump into Legendary Pokémon Palkia or Dialga! There are more than 490 Pokémon in Pokémon Diamond and Pokémon Pearl. But be on the lookout for Team Galactic, a dastardly group that is trying to kidnap Pokémon.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Pokemon Diamond-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20070422T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Game Freak</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure, Role-Playing</genre>
		<players>4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pokemon Mystery Dungeon - Blue Rescue Team.nds</path>
		<name>Pokémon Mystery Dungeon: Blue Rescue Team</name>
		<desc>Pokémon Mystery Dungeon opens with the player (formerly a human) waking up as a Pokémon. The Pokémon that woke him up explains that he found the player just like that; unconscious on a field. The player quickly comes to the realization that he has been turned into a Pokémon, but apparently has amnesia (except for the memory that he was previously a human). The partner explains that the Pokémon world has recently been riddled with natural disasters (these disasters are also preventing Pokémon from evolving). Just then, a Butterfree flies up, and in a frenzy asks the two to help her find her lost child, a Caterpie. After saving the child, the partner and player Pokémon decide to form a Rescue Team.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Pokemon Mystery Dungeon - Blue Rescue Team-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20060918T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Chunsoft</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pokemon Mystery Dungeon - Explorers of Darkness.nds</path>
		<name>Pokémon Mystery Dungeon: Explorers of Darkness</name>
		<desc>In this pair of action-packed adventures, players journey as actual Pokemon through a fantastic land untouched by humans. Before the game starts, players take a test to help them figure out which of 16 Pokemon best represents their personalities. Players then experience their adventure through the eyes of a Pokemon as they explore the land and embark on an epic journey through time and darkness. They talk and team up with other Pokemon to set out on an epic voyage while navigating an endless array of randomly generated dungeons. More than 490 Pokemon populate these new games, guaranteeing strategic, intense battles and infinite possibilities, no matter which Pokemon players become. To widen their circle of Pokemon friends, Nintendo Wi-Fi Connection lets users engage in wireless rescue operations and send alerts to their friends via e-mail or mobile text message.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Pokemon Mystery Dungeon - Explorers of Darkness-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20080420T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Chunsoft</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pokemon Mystery Dungeon - Explorers of Sky.nds</path>
		<name>Pokémon Mystery Dungeon: Explorers of Sky</name>
		<desc>Pokemon Mystery Dungeon: Explorers of Sky expands on the fun found in Pokemon Mystery Dungeon: Explorers of Time and Pokemon Mystery Dungeon: Explorers of Darkness. Players become a Pokemon and team up with a partner Pokemon. Together the two set out on an adventure of exploration and discovery, ultimately saving the world from destruction.

With additional Pokemon to become, new Special Episodes and enhanced communication features, this is a grand adventure with a moving story and stunning finale. This game is a great starting point for players to enter the world of Pokemon Mystery Dungeon and for returning players to discover even more secrets.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Pokemon Mystery Dungeon - Explorers of Sky-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20091012T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Chunsoft</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pokemon Mystery Dungeon - Explorers of Time.nds</path>
		<name>Pokémon Mystery Dungeon: Explorers of Time</name>
		<desc>Which Pokémon are you? Another amazing addition to the Pokémon series but this time you get to be the Pokémon! You are in control of your own adventure in the latest release of Pokémon Mystery Dungeon: Explorers of Time! For years you've captured, traded and battled with them; now it's time once again to become a Pokémon yourself! Join a guild and prepare for adventure as you return to a fantastic land untouched by humans. Hundreds of Pokémon, randomly-generated dungeons, and online compatibility enhance strategic exploration and battles. Head out to explore long-lost dungeons, or hunt down criminal Pokémon - the choice is yours in this epic game.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Pokemon Mystery Dungeon - Explorers of Time-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20080420T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Chunsoft</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pokemon SoulSilver.nds</path>
		<name>Pokémon SoulSilver Version</name>
		<desc>Pokemon HeartGold Version and Pokemon SoulSilver Version return players to the scenic Johto region first introduced in the beloved original Pokemon Gold and Pokemon Silver games nearly a decade ago. The richly detailed adventure of Pokemon Gold and Pokemon Silver is now enhanced for the Nintendo DS and Nintendo DSi systems with updated graphics and sound, as well as new touch-screen features and a host of surprises. Pokemon HeartGold Version and Pokemon SoulSilver Version bring dozens of Pokemon characters back into the limelight for a new Pokemon generation - and longtime fans - to catch, train and battle.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Pokemon SoulSilver-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20090912T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Game Freak</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure, Role-Playing</genre>
		<players>4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Rayman - Raving Rabbids.nds</path>
		<name>Rayman Raving Rabbids</name>
		<desc>Rayman Raving Rabbids marks the return of the iconic video-game hero, Rayman, in his funniest and zaniest adventure ever. When the world of Rayman is threatened by a devastating invasion of crazed, out-of-control bunnies Rayman must rise up against his furry foes to foil their wicked plans. Utilizing an array of amazing new abilities, and with the help of magical creatures, Rayman must break out all the moves to save his world from these delirious bunnies and their hare-raising antics.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Rayman - Raving Rabbids-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20070306T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ubisoft</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Retro Game Challenge.nds</path>
		<name>Retro Game Challenge</name>
		<desc>Thrown back in time to the 1980's, you are turned into a young boy and forced to play video games by an evil self-proclaimed "Game Master", Game Master Arino. Game Master Arino will test your gaming skills by throwing various challenges at you in a wide-variety of retro games including shooters, racing, action and even an epic role-playing game - your only way to return is to defeat him in every retro game challenge he throws at you.

But you are not alone in your quest-armed with access to gaming magazines, cheat codes can be found to warp to later levels, receive unlimited continues or even become invincible! A young Arino is at your side to keep you company during your challenges, quite amused at the fact that he grows up to be so evil in the future to be the cause of your current predicament. Test your skills with the awesomeness of the 8-bit era and prevent the retro games from exacting their revenge! An original game based on the popular Japanese GAME CENTER CX TV series, Retro Game Challenge reinvents how classic games are played by having the player complete short challenges in a wide-variety of games to keep the game play fresh and rewarding.

Specific challenges in shooters, racing, action and a role-playing game are integrated into the story, while the in-game magazines offer cheat codes as well as fake 80's news stories paying tribute to the rich history of the gaming industry. Whether it's 80's nostalgia for the seasoned gamer or experiencing classic 8-bit game play for the first time, Retro Game Challenge has something for everyone.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Retro Game Challenge-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20090210T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Indies Zero</developer>
		<publisher>XSEED Games</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure, Role-Playing, Racing, Shooter</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sims 2.nds</path>
		<name>The Sims 2: Apartment Pets</name>
		<desc>The Sims 2 Apartment Pets is a video game for the Nintendo DS video game console. EA has described it as a follow-up to The Sims 2 Pets for the Nintendo DS. As in the original, it allows a diverse amount of customization, allowing pets to be created in a variety of colors and sizes.

The Sims 2: Apartment Pets is a combination of The Sims 2: Apartment Life and The Sims 2: Pets. Before beginning the game the player must create a Sim in Create-A-Sim, but with very limited options compared to other games in the series. It is quite unique compared to other games in the series.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Sims 2-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20080826T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Full Fat Games</developer>
		<publisher>EA Games</publisher>
		<genre>Life Simulation</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sims 3.nds</path>
		<name>The Sims 3</name>
		<desc>The Sims return yet again in this third full evolution of the long-running and always-expanding sim series. In this home console version of The Sims 3, players will be able to create Sims with unique personalities, fulfill their desires (... or not,) and control their lives within a living neighborhood. Additionally, all-new features make it easier than ever to mess with life as players can unlock the ultimate "Karma Powers" for instant control and unleash them on their Sims. Players can help their Sim "get lucky," bless them with "instant beauty" or be deviant and curse them with an "epic fail." But players should use these powers wisely—they may have unexpected results and karma may come back to bite.

With the Nintendo DS version of the game, players can use the stylus to build their Sims' homes with tools, draw walls and floors, and customize virtually everything from décor objects, textures, and more. Players will use the stylus to sculpt their Sims’ facial features, choose hair styles and clothing, and dictate personalities in the most robust Create a Sim yet for a handheld game. In Story Mode, players will control multiple Sims within a family and enjoy life's special moments. For the first time ever on the Nintendo DS, players can enjoy a complete life simulation as they guide their Sims through completing challenges to unlock additional items, new buildings and landmarks, and more.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Sims 3-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20101026T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>The Sims Studio, Exient</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Life Simulation</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sonic Chronicles - The Dark Brotherhood.nds</path>
		<name>Sonic Chronicles: The Dark Brotherhood</name>
		<desc>The game initially focuses on the events surrounding the kidnapping of Knuckles and the disappearance of the Chaos Emeralds after the defeat of Doctor Eggman, before moving on to follow the cast of characters across two dimensions as they encounter a new ally, Shade the Echidna, and seek to stop the invasion of their world by Ix, the leader of Shade's tribe, the Nocturnus.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Sonic Chronicles - The Dark Brotherhood-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20080930T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>BioWare</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sonic Rush.nds</path>
		<name>Sonic Rush</name>
		<desc>Sonic the Hedgehog has a new partner, Blaze the Cat, in this fast-paced platformer, Sonic Rush. You can play as either Sonic or Blaze as you try to track down powerful Sol emeralds. Sonic Rush displays the level over both screens, allowing for screen-spanning jumps and dives. Some gameplay modes include stylus support as well.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Sonic Rush-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20051115T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Dimps Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Platform</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sonic Rush Adventure.nds</path>
		<name>Sonic Rush Adventure</name>
		<desc>Sonic returns to the DS with all the classic 2D dual screen action of "Sonic Rush," as well as a new high-seas adventure where he clashes with ruthless pirates. As Sonic, set off from Windmill Village to explore seven islands for action-packed adventures spread across a large map. As you venture, you'll uncover valuable items and materials that will help Tails build new ships so that Sonic can track down the villainous pirates in a variety of ways.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Sonic Rush Adventure-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20070918T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Platform</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Spectrobes.nds</path>
		<name>Spectrobes</name>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Spectrobes-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20071106T000000</releasedate>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Spectrobes - Beyond the Portals.nds</path>
		<name>Spectrobes: Beyond the Portals</name>
		<desc>Spectrobes: Beyond The Portals is the sequel to popular anime-inspired, sci-fi action/role playing game series Spectrobes, for Nintendo DS. Spectrobes: Beyond The Portals continues the story of Rallen and Jeena, interplanetary patrol officers who discover, excavate, awaken and train mysterious fossilized creatures known as spectrobes and then use them to battle enemies. The story revolves around the origins of ominous portals that lead to distant dimensions and a new nemesis who hopes to destroy the spectrobes.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Spectrobes - Beyond the Portals-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20081007T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Jupiter Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>Disney Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./SpongeBob SquarePants - Creature from the Krusty Krab.nds</path>
		<name>SpongeBob SquarePants: Creature from the Krusty Krab</name>
		<desc>Bikini Bottom will never be the same. SpongeBob SquarePants: Creature from the Krusty Krab brings the #1 kids gaming franchise and TV property into the bizarre and unusual, introducing never-before-seen art styles and brand new gameplay mechanics that will change your perception of Bikini Bottom forever. Embark on a series of fantastic tales through nine visually unique levels. Experience five brand new gameplay mechanics including rampaging, flying, skydiving, chase and hot rod racing. Rampage through Bikini Bottom as gigantic Plankton. Fly through the savage jaw of the enormous bull worm as SpongeBob. Blast off into outer space and survive a hi-speed asteroid field as Patrick. Plunge into the pages of a comic book as Starfishman and become the hero of the seven seas. Speed through the metallic flames, chrome and smoke-filled world of Hot Rod racing.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/SpongeBob SquarePants - Creature from the Krusty Krab-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20061018T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>WayForward Technologies</developer>
		<publisher>THQ</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./SpongeBob SquarePants - Plankton's Robotic Revenge.nds</path>
		<name>SpongeBob SquarePants: Plankton's Robotic Revenge</name>
		<desc>Blending exploration, combat, and puzzle-solving, SpongeBob SquarePants: Plankton's Robotic Revenge features references and humor from the hit Nickelodeon TV animated series. Gamers of all ages and skill levels can get together with co-op party mode, creating an experience that's fun for one, but better with others. Fans can choose between their favorite characters like SpongeBob, Patrick, Squidward, Sandy, or Mr. Krabs as they scour the town hunting for hidden collectibles.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/SpongeBob SquarePants - Plankton's Robotic Revenge-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20131022T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Behavior Interactive, Engine Software</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure, Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./SpongeBob SquarePants - The Yellow Avenger.nds</path>
		<name>SpongeBob Squarepants: The Yellow Avenger</name>
		<desc>SpongeBob acquires Mermaid Man's powers when he wears his belt. Unfortunately SpongeBob accidentally puts the Dirty Bubble into a washing machine with the belt, which causes him to split into countless dirty bubbles. SpongeBob has to stop villains such as Manray, The Sinister Slug, The Jumbo Shrimp, Atomic Flounder, and Dirty Bubble, using Mermaid Man's powers to save Bikini Bottom. The story is divided into Acts, each with a different villain trying to wreak havoc on Bikini Bottom: Manray wants to flood Goo Lagoon; Sinister Slug has an evil plan to stop the talent show; Jumbo Shrimp, with the help of Plankton, creates a machine to shrink people; The Atomic Flounder causes chaos in Industrial Park; and The Dirty Bubble returns with the machine the Jumbo Shrimp used in the third act. He plans to hit SpongeBob with more Little Dirty Bubbles.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/SpongeBob SquarePants - The Yellow Avenger-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20051107T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tantalus Media</developer>
		<publisher>THQ</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure, Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./SpongeBob SquarePants featuring Nicktoons - Globs of Doom.nds</path>
		<name>SpongeBob SquarePants Featuring Nicktoons: Globs of Doom</name>
		<desc>SpongeBob SquarePants featuring Nicktoons: Globs of Doom (commonly shortened to simply Nicktoons: Globs of Doom) is a 2008 video game, the fourth and final installment in the Nicktoons Unite! series, and the last Nicktoons video game to be published by the original THQ company, before the company became defunct in 2013. Characters from SpongeBob SquarePants, Danny Phantom, The Adventures of Jimmy Neutron: Boy Genius, Tak and the Power of Juju, and Invader Zim appear. This is the only Nicktoons Unite! game to not feature characters from The Fairly OddParents. The original developers of the previous games for consoles did not come back to create this installment.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/SpongeBob SquarePants featuring Nicktoons - Globs of Doom-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20081028T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Natsume</developer>
		<publisher>THQ</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./SpongeBob's Boating Bash.nds</path>
		<name>SpongeBob's Boating Bash</name>
		<desc>SpongeBob SquarePants is in for the bumpiest ride of his life! SpongeBob's Boating Bash draws upon one of the most popular events in the TV series - SpongeBob's tireless tenacity to earn his boating license. After failing the boating exam 78 times, a shady shark character tricks SpongeBob into taking the zany D.R.I.V.E. course that will send him and his friends steering out of control. In this fast-paced, demolition derby style party game, players will drive around in boat mobiles and compete in wacky arenas throughout Bikini Bottom to be the last boat standing.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/SpongeBob's Boating Bash-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20100302T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Firebrand Games</developer>
		<publisher>THQ</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./SpongeBob's Truth or Square.nds</path>
		<name>SpongeBob's Truth or Square</name>
		<desc>SpongeBob's Truth or Square is a video game based on the SpongeBob SquarePants episode with the same title. It was released on October 26, 2009 for SpongeBob's 10th anniversary. It reuses many assets from Battle for Bikini Bottom and The SpongeBob SquarePants Movie, including music, textures and models.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/SpongeBob's Truth or Square-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20091026T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>THQ</developer>
		<publisher>THQ</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure, Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Spore Creatures.nds</path>
		<name>Spore Creatures</name>
		<desc>SPORE takes players on an epic journey from the origin and evolution of life through the development of civilization and eventually into the outer reaches of space. Create a creature, then control every dimension of its evolution from pond scum to galactic god. Experience multiple styles of gameplay as your creature advances through different stages of development. Fight for survival in the wild, develop a sprawling metropolis, trade and war against rival civilizations and explore the outer reaches of the galaxy. Every aspect of the universe from creatures to vehicles, buildings to plants, are created by the player and automatically shared with other players, providing a limitless number of worlds to explore and play. Create, control and explore your universe with SPORE.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Spore Creatures-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20080907T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Griptonite Games</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Construction and Management Simulation, Strategy</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Spore Hero Arena.nds</path>
		<name>Spore Hero Arena</name>
		<desc>An evil force is wreaking havoc across the galaxy, and only you can stop it! For the first time ever, build fully 3D Spore creatures on your Nintendo DS and take them into battle. Explore planets all over the galaxy, fight creatures, and gather parts to customize and enhance your mighty hero. Compete in a variety of arena battles against dangerous enemies in your quest to become the Galactic Champion and save the galaxy!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Spore Hero Arena-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20091006T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Maxis Software</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Spyro - Shadow Legacy .nds</path>
		<name>Spyro: Shadow Legacy</name>
		<desc>Spyro Shadow Legacy introduces role playing elements to the Dragon Realms, offering Spyro fans an "RPG light" experience with all new gameplay features. By fighting and defeating creatures in the game, players earn experience points that improve Spyro's strength and abilities. This RPG element allows players to use their experience to build Spyro’s new magical powers and martial arts combat abilities as the game progresses.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Spyro - Shadow Legacy -image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20051018T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Amaze Entertainment, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Vivendi Games</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Star Fox Command.nds</path>
		<name>Star Fox Command</name>
		<desc>Star Fox Command lets you hop into your fight through a unique branching storyline of missions, all rendered in gorgeous 3-D. This game brings a whole new strategic element to the series, with a commander's view of the mission. Using the touch screen, players can draw the routes they and their teammates will take. Battle the enemies they encounter as they take over bases and strategically advance across the map. Players can also blow their friends out of the sky, as they dogfight 8 players over a local wireless connection -- or take on 4 players from around the world on Nintendo Wi-Fi Connection.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Star Fox Command-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20060828T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Q-Games</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Flight Simulator</genre>
		<players>4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Star Wars - Battlefront - Elite Squadron.nds</path>
		<name>Star Wars Battlefront: Elite Squadron</name>
		<desc>Elite Squadron allows players to participate in combat on foot, in ground vehicles or in space. Players are also able to enter capital ships and, once the shields are down, fight the enemy inside on foot. The ground-space transitions are accompanied by short cutscenes while the game loads the next area.[2] The same is also true of entering or exiting a capital ship.[3] This is the first Battlefront game to allow players to fly from ground to space battles.[4] The consequences of each battle will depend on the players actions, meaning that each individual enemy killed can affect the outcome of a result.[2] The battlefront will not be one giant, seamless map, but a compilation of inter-connected, smaller size areas, each one capable of affecting the other</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Star Wars - Battlefront - Elite Squadron-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20091103T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>n-Space, Inc</developer>
		<publisher>LucasArts Entertainment Company LLC</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Shooter</genre>
		<players>4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tak - Mojo Mistake.nds</path>
		<name>Tak: Mojo Mistake</name>
		<desc>Tak finds himself exhausted from trying to help everyone in his village. He decided to use his Juju magic to create little helpers called Hackies. But when these little critters became unruly and then unexpectedly multiplied into hundreds, they invaded both the Pupununu village and the Juju realm causing havoc and devastation. Now Tak must do all he can to get rid of the troublemakers and restore balance to both worlds!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Tak - Mojo Mistake-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20081013T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>THQ</developer>
		<publisher>THQ</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tak - The Great Juju Challenge.nds</path>
		<name>Tak: The Great Juju Challenge</name>
		<desc>On your mark. Get Set. Juju!!

Once each generation, the world's mightiest heroes, fiercest warriors, and most powerful athletes gather together to compete in The Great Juju Challenge. Play as both Tak and Lok in the fight for the championship and the future of the Pupanunu people.

Features

• Play as both Tak and Lok in all-new 3-D adventure!
• Upgrade your Juju Magic to make your spells and abilities even more powerful
• Use the DS Touch Screen and microphone for tons of replayable mini-games
• Race to the finish line in an all-new derby mode!
• Unlock new secrets like the Shaman puzzle game!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Tak - The Great Juju Challenge-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20050919T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>THQ</developer>
		<publisher>THQ</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ultimate Mortal Kombat.nds</path>
		<name>Ultimate Mortal Kombat</name>
		<desc>Ultimate Mortal Kombat combines the visceral thrills of the classic "Ultimate Mortal Kombat 3" and the addictive puzzle action of the Puzzle Kombat component of Midway's best-selling "Mortal Kombat: Deception" in a single DS-friendly package. With new record-keeping capability, and Nintendo Wi-Fi Connection multiplayer, players can take UMK anywhere for fighting action on the go.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Ultimate Mortal Kombat-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20071112T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Other Ocean Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Midway Games</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Up.nds</path>
		<name>UP</name>
		<desc>Journey through the undiscovered jungles of South America, in Up the video game. You can control Russell, Carl, Dug the talking dog and a female bird named Kevin, or you can play with a friend through the entire game. Aided by Russell¿s wilderness knowledge, the four characters must work together to navigate treacherous jungle terrain, combat exotic animals and avoid being captured. Each character has special abilities that help in their journey. During the game, you will explore exciting environments, overcome obstacles and battle beasts in an effort to stop Muntz from capturing Kevin.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Up-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20090526T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Altron Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>THQ</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Wario - Master of Disguise.nds</path>
		<name>Wario: Master of Disguise</name>
		<desc>The world's most low-down and ornery garlic-lover never lets a get-rich quick scheme pass him by. Wario: Master of Disguise opens with our money-mad hero taking a break from being a shady software impresario to watch a TV show about a master thief. Working himself up into a lather of jealousy, Wario leaps through the screen and embarks on his own glamorous globe-trotting career as a thief.
With the helpful advice of a mustachioed magic wand named Goodstyle, you'll soon learn how to use your DS stylus to draw specific designs on Wario to give him new costumes. Break into exotic locations, from a luxury liner &amp; watery ruins to an Egyptian pyramid, all in the hopes of grabbing as much treasure and loot as Wario can carry.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Wario - Master of Disguise-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20070305T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Suzak</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./WarioWare - D.I.Y..nds</path>
		<name>WarioWare D.I.Y.</name>
		<desc>This game, which puts the concept of user-generated content on center stage, allows players to design their own micro-games from scratch. Every element, such as the characters, the environment, the actions and even the purpose of the micro-game itself, is controlled entirely by the player. Players will then be able to share their completed micro-games with other WarioWare D.I.Y. owners.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/WarioWare - D.I.Y.-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20100328T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Intelligent Systems Co., Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Puzzle</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./WarioWare - Touched!.nds</path>
		<name>WarioWare: Touched!</name>
		<desc>Wario makes his debut on the Nintendo DS with hundreds of all-new minigames. Now you must complete your goals by using the touch screen and a stylus. Tap, scratch, and rub your stylus on the touch screen to play minigames that have you do everything from milking a cow and drawing a mustache to hurling stars at evil ninjas. You can even play some minigames by blowing into the DS's built-in microphone. The more minigames you clear, the more characters and items you unlock.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/WarioWare - Touched!-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20050214T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Puzzle</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Yoshi's Island DS.nds</path>
		<name>Yoshi's Island DS</name>
		<desc>Yoshi's Island DS is a sequel to the SNES game, Yoshi's Island. In it, players control Yoshi as he travels to Kamek's castle to rescue Luigi. Yoshi can carry Baby Mario, Peach, DK, Wario or Bowser on his back - depending on the baby carried, Yoshi will gain a special ability; for example, Mario lets Yoshi dash, Peach allows Yoshi to float for a longer period of time, and Wario whips out a gigantic magnet to attract coins and other metallic objects. If Yoshi is hit by an enemy, a counter appears, and begins to slowly count down to zero. If it reaches zero, the baby is kidnapped, and Yoshi loses a life. Yoshi can increase his counter by collecting stars that are rewards for some puzzles and defeating certain enemies.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Yoshi's Island DS-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20061113T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Artoon Co., Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Advance Wars - Days of Ruin.nds</path>
		<name>Advance Wars: Days of Ruin</name>
		<desc>Days of Ruin takes place in an entirely new world where a large-scale meteor shower triggered massive global destruction that eradicated 90 percent of the population. After the catastrophe, the survivors have formed together into militaristic bands that are warring over the last remaining scraps of civilization. You'll take control of Will, a young military cadet (whose hair is admittedly just a little spiky) who quickly becomes embroiled in the conflict at the outset of the game.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Advance Wars - Days of Ruin-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20080121T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Intelligent Systems Co., Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20210219T155644</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pokemon Pearl.nds</path>
		<name>Pokémon Pearl Version</name>
		<desc>Welcome to the next generation of Pokemon!
As a rookie Pokemon Trainer, you'll need to catch, train, and battle Pokemon on your journey to become the Pokemon League Champion. You will face many challenges along the way, as you search for the Pokemon that rules space in Pokemon Pearl Version.
Discover more than 100 new Pokemon in the Sinnoh Region!
Meet goals and earn the ability to import Pokemon from your GBA Versions!
Battle and Trade with your friends around the world using Nintendo Wi-Fi Connection!
Watch as day turns to night with the return of the real-time clock feature!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Pokemon Pearl-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20070422T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Game Freak</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure, Role-Playing</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20210220T162755</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./sunshine-ds.nds</path>
		<name>sunshine-ds</name>
		<playcount>2</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20210304T145614</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Metroid Prime - Hunters.nds</path>
		<name>Metroid Prime: Hunters</name>
		<desc>The famous Metroid series lands on the Nintendo DS with Metroid Prime: Hunters. A once-strong race has gone extinct, leaving powerful artifacts to be found by bounty hunters from across the galaxy. The game features a variety of bounty hunters, both old and new, to the series. It also features multiple competitive game modes--such as deathmatch and king of the hill--for battling wirelessly with up to three other players.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Metroid Prime - Hunters-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20060320T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo Software Technology</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Shooter</genre>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20210313T071234</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Cooking Mama.nds</path>
		<name>Cooking Mama</name>
		<desc>The gameplay structure consists of the player progressing through a series of short minigames. The game features a total of 96 different dishes.

Each minigame represents a different activity in the meal preparation, such as mixing, frying, or chopping the provided ingredients. The minigame mechanics themselves range from quickly drawing parallel lines in order to chop items, to a rhythm game where ingredients are added to a skillet or the heat is adjusted at precisely the right time. In many cases, players must look at the top screen of the DS for guidance on what to do next and then perform the task on the bottom screen. If the player makes a serious blunder or time expires without sufficient progress being made, that step in the cooking process is considered a failure. When this happens, a graphic of an angry "Mama" with flames erupting from her eyes is displayed, along with the caption "Don't worry, Mama will fix it!".</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Cooking Mama-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20060912T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Office Create</developer>
		<publisher>Majesco Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Life Simulation</genre>
		<playcount>2</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20210412T204730</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pokemon HeartGold.nds</path>
		<name>Pokémon HeartGold Version</name>
		<desc>Pokémon HeartGold is an enhanced remake of one of the second installments in the Pokémon Main RPG Series, Pokémon Gold.


Set in the region of Johto, the player controls a new Pokémon Trainer on his/her way to meet up with Pokémon Researcher Professor Elm at his lab to receive his/her first Pokémon. While running an errand for Elm, the player returns to find that a thief has stolen one of the professor's Pokémon. This event starts your quest to becoming a Pokémon master, leading you through the region of Johto and later Kanto, to battle the mysterious Team Rocket and capture all 493 Pokémon. 


Along with retaining most of the original game's features, HeartGold contains quite a few new updates. Like Gold the story will incorporate the legendary Pokémon Ho-Oh (who can be seen on the game's box art), although this time in a bigger fashion. Graphics have been upgraded to 3D models to resemble the series previous Nintendo DS iterations, Diamond, Pearl, and Platinum. The ability to have any one of your Pokémon following you on the Overworld Screen which was limitedly seen in Pokémon Yellow has been added. 


Included with the game is a peripheral known as the Pokéwalker. Acting as a pedometer, the Pokéwalker allows you to wirelessly transfer a Pokémon from HeartGold to it. When there is a Pokémon in the Pokéwalker it gains "experience points" for each step you take. The player also earns a form of money known as "watts", which is used to help catch other Pokémon and buy items.

The game is compatible with the following games via Nintendo Wi-Fi Connection: Pokémon SoulSilver, Diamond, Pearl, and Platinum.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Pokemon HeartGold-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20090912T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Game Freak</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure, Role-Playing</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20210421T005452</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Diddy Kong Racing DS.nds</path>
		<name>Diddy Kong Racing DS</name>
		<desc>A bloated space pig has taken control of Diddy Kong's Island paradise and only you can stop his nefarious plot! Take on the racing challenge of a lifetime as you drive, hover and fly your way across the massive island. This remastered take on a Nintendo 64 classic is sure to rev the engines of adventure racing fans everywhere!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Diddy Kong Racing DS-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20070207T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rare, Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20210604T151631</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Mario 64 DS.nds</path>
		<name>Super Mario 64 DS</name>
		<desc>Super Mario 64, the classic 3D platformer for the Nintendo 64, arrives on the Nintendo DS with all-new features that take advantage of the portable system's dual screens, touch screen, and wireless multiplayer capability. Like the original game, Super Mario 64 DS challenges you to find all the power stars hidden throughout the royal castle in the effort to free Peach imprisoned inside the castle. This time, you can play as Mario, Luigi, Wario, and Yoshi, each of whom has unique abilities. Overcome the challenges on your own or battle up to three of your friends in the multiplayer modes.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Super Mario 64 DS-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20041121T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20211222T015448</lastplayed>
	</game>
</gameList>
