<?xml version="1.0"?>
<gameList>
	<game>
		<path>./Kirby's Star Stacker (USA, Europe) (SGB Enhanced).gb</path>
		<name>Kirby's Star Stacker (USA, Europe) (SGB Enhanced)</name>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20201102T142745</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Intertale.gb</path>
		<name>Intertale</name>
		<playcount>3</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20201106T043118</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Kirby's Dream Land.gb</path>
		<name>Kirby's Dream Land</name>
		<desc>The gluttonous King Dedede has stolen all of the food from the inhabitants of Dream Land for a midnight feast, so Kirby, a resident of Dream Land, goes to retrieve the food and stop Dedede. Kirby's Dream Land plays like other platformers of the 8-bit and 16-bit era of video games: Kirby must use various natural abilities and occasionally external abilities or items while heading toward the goal at the end of each level. Like many 1980s-era platformers, the player can accumulate points, with an extra life granted when the player has enough points. However, because Kirby lacks a save function, scores are not recorded. Also, there are no save files, so the player has to start over again when the Game Boy is turned off, if the player chooses to return to the title screen after a Game Over, or if the player resets the game. All levels are played on a two-dimensional plane, letting Kirby move only left, right, up, and down. Kirby can walk, jump, and fly. Kirby can also inhale objects and enemies, swallowing them or spitting them out as projectiles.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Kirby's Dream Land-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19920801T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>HAL Laboratory</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Kirby's Dream Land 2.gb</path>
		<name>Kirby's Dream Land 2</name>
		<desc>The Rainbow Bridges have disappeared! Help Kirby solve the mystery. Search the seven Rainbow Islands while battling King DeDeDe and his horde of evil minions! Meet Rick the Hamster, Kine the Fish and Coo the Owl. Each holds important abilities that can multiply the magnitude of Kirby's powers. Earn the mysterious Rainbow Sword and prepare to face Kirby's most menacing rival ever - the evil Dark Matter!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Kirby's Dream Land 2-image.png</image>
		<releasedate>19950501T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>HAL Laboratory</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Kirby's Pinball Land.gb</path>
		<name>Kirby's Pinball Land</name>
		<desc>Choose your world and take aim! Kirby will be launched into the fast-paced danger of uncharted worlds, but you can help him face his foes head on. It's a pinball race to check out each new world's surprise enemies and pitfalls. Flip Kirby in battles against lethal eyeballs, a shooting tree and mace-swinging maniacs. Take aim and leap to new worlds!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Kirby's Pinball Land-image.png</image>
		<releasedate>19940304T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>HAL Laboratory</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Kirby's Star Stacker.gb</path>
		<name>Kirby's Star Stacker</name>
		<desc>Join Kirby as he stacks the falling stars with help from his friends, Rick the Hamster, Kine the Sunfish, and Coo the Owl. Watch out for King Dedede. He is out to stop you! With a few quick moves and some well-timed strategy, you can quickly outwit him and move on to the next challenging level. Kirby's Star Stacker features pure puzzle fun for everyone. From above, blocks rain down constantly. From below, whole lines appear with unrelenting clock-like regularity. Simply sandwich the stars between Kirby's pals and you'll soon be on your way to the high score.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Kirby's Star Stacker-image.png</image>
		<releasedate>19970401T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>HAL Laboratory</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Legend of Zelda - Link's Awakening.gb</path>
		<name>The Legend of Zelda : Link's Awakening</name>
		<desc>The fourth game in the Zelda series although it does not take place in Hyrule. After being attacked at sea, Link's ship sinks, and he finds himself stranded on Koholint Island. He awakens to see a beautiful woman looking down at him. He soon learns the island has a giant egg on top of a mountain that the Wind Fish inhabits deep inside. Link is told to "awaken the wind fish and all will be answered," so Link sets out on another quest.

Play is similar to the SNES game with a top down perspective. Link must go onto each of the 7 temples to retrieve a musical instrument that will help awaken the Wind Fish. Along the way, Link must search the land and uncover hidden treasures and items that will allow him to progress on his journey. With new items, he can open up new passages that will take him even farther on his quest and allow him to enter new areas that were inaccessible before. Link can attack his enemies with his sword or use items he finds during his quest to help him. Guarding every instrument is a temple boss, which must be defeated if Link is to awaken the Wind Fish.
</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Legend of Zelda - Link's Awakening-image.png</image>
		<rating>0.95</rating>
		<releasedate>19930606T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pokemon - Blue Version.gb</path>
		<name>Pokémon Blue Version</name>
		<desc>You’ve finally been granted your Pokémon trainer’s license.  Now, it’s time to head out to become the world’s greatest Pokémon trainer.  It’s going to take all you’ve got to collect 150 Pokémon in this enormous world.  Catch and train monsters like the shockingly-cute Pikachu.  Face off against Blastoise’s torrential water cannons.  Stand strong when facing Pidgeot’s stormy Gust.  Trade with friends and watch your Pokémon evolve.  Important—no single Pokémon can win it all.  Can you develop the ultimate Pokémon strategy to defeat the eight GYM Leaders and become the greatest Pokémon Master of all time?

• Collect up to 139 different Pokémon playing the Blue version.  Using the Game Link cable, trade with a friend who has the Red version to capture all 150.
• You’ll need to use both versions (Red and Blue) to collect all of the Pokémon.
• Test your training skills by battling against a friend using the Game Link cable.
• Save your Pokémon and game progress on the Game Pak memory.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Pokemon - Blue Version-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19961015T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Game Freak</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure, Role-Playing</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pokemon - Green Version.gb</path>
		<name>Pokémon Green Version</name>
		<desc>You've finally been granted your Pokemon trainer's license. Now, it's time to head out to become the world's greatest Pokemon trainer. It's going to take all you've got to collect 150 Pokemon in this enormous world. Catch and train monsters like the shockingly-cute Pikachu. Face off against Blastoise's torrential water cannons. Stand strong when facing Pidgeot's stormy Gust. Trade with friends and watch your Pokemon evolve. Important - no single Pokemon can win it all. Can you develop the ultimate Pokemon strategy to defeat the 8 GYM Leaders and become the greatest Pokemon Master of all time?</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Pokemon - Green Version-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19960227T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Game Freak</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure, Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tamagotchi.gb</path>
		<name>Tamagotchi</name>
		<desc>Now there's a whole new way to experience all of the fun and excitement of America's favorite digital pet with Tamagotchi for your Nintendo Game Boy. With the Game Boy version, you can raise up to 3 Tamagotchi at one time. You can change your Tamagotchi's growth rate, save unfinished games so that you can return to them later and enter your Tamagotchi in tournaments! There are also more ways to care for your Tamagotchi than with the original toy!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Tamagotchi-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19971001T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tom Create</developer>
		<publisher>Bandai Co., Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Life Simulation</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pokemon - Red Version.gb</path>
		<name>Pokémon Red Version</name>
		<desc>You’ve finally been granted your Pokémon trainer’s license.  Now, it’s time to head out to become the world’s greatest Pokémon trainer.  It’s going to take all you’ve got to collect 150 Pokémon in this enormous world.  Catch and train monsters like the shockingly-cute Pikachu.  Face off against Blastoise’s torrential water cannons.  Stand strong when facing Pidgeot’s stormy Gust.  Trade with friends and watch your Pokémon evolve.  Important—no single Pokémon can win it all.  Can you develop the ultimate Pokémon strategy to defeat the eight GYM Leaders and become the greatest Pokémon Master of all time?

• Collect up to 139 different Pokémon playing the Red version.  Using the Game Link cable, trade with a friend who has the Blue version to capture all 150.
• You’ll need to use both versions (Red and Blue) to collect all of the Pokémon.
• Test your training skills by battling against a friend using the Game Link cable.
• Save your Pokémon and game progress on the Game Pak memory.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Pokemon - Red Version-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19980928T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Game Freak</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure, Role-Playing</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20210220T163442</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pokémon_Gold_-_Spaceworld_1997_Demo_(NonDebug).7z</path>
		<name>Pokémon_Gold_-_Spaceworld_1997_Demo_(NonDebug)</name>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20210304T054750</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pokemon - Spaceworld Gold Version.gb</path>
		<name>Pokemon - Spaceworld Gold Version</name>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20210304T055149</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tetris - Minuet Version.gb</path>
		<name>Tetris</name>
		<desc>Tetris is a puzzle video game which was released in 1989 by Nintendo for the Game Boy. Geometric shapes fall from the top of a playfield to rest on the bottom; fit the pieces together and the formed line will disappear. If the pieces are not lined up correctly they eventually stack up to the top of the playfield and the game is over. Difficulty increases by dropping the pieces faster and faster over time. Tetris is a verifiable classic game, translated to well over 200 electronic and computer platforms. It takes 2 minutes to learn, but a lifetime to master!

* Game Link

* Game Boy Color has preset color palettes saved internally for Tetris and some other original GB games. This gives some variation in color when played on GBC.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Tetris - Minuet Version-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19890731T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Bullet-Proof Software, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<playcount>2</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20210313T061331</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Metroid II - Return of Samus (World).gb</path>
		<name>Metroid II - Return of Samus (World)</name>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20210313T064921</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Metroid II DX - Return of Samus (World).gb</path>
		<name>Metroid II DX: Return of Samus</name>
		<desc>A Sinister Planet Threatens the Galaxy!

Space Hunter Samus Aran returns to battle a planet crawling with evil creatures bent on universal domination in this bigger than ever sequel to the NES classic, Metroid.

Take control! Guide Samus through cavernous corridors, ancient ruins and alien traps. On the mysterious planet of the Metroids, you'll find artifacts of a lost civilization that grant amazing powers. Cut through creatures in a buzz-saw blur! Roll through hidden tunnels and climb sheer walls!

A battery back-up allows you to save your progress as you fight to the heart of the planet and search for the merciless Metroid leaders. If you are a cunning explorer, you'll earn the best of several super endings.

Enter this exciting Metroid sequel and experience the thrills of Game Boy like never before!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Metroid II DX - Return of Samus (World)-image.png</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19911101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo R&amp;D1</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure, Shooter, Platform</genre>
		<playcount>3</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20210313T180803</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Kirby's Block Ball.gb</path>
		<name>Kirby's Block Ball</name>
		<desc>Kirby's back with fast-paced, four-way action!

It's a breakaway bash in this wild new Kirby game of Block Ball! By destroying the blocks on the screen, you clear stages and obtain powers that help you in your final confrontation with King Dedede.

Paddles on all four sides of the screen make this an intense four-way action contest. Your quick reactions and your careful use of Kirby's powers will determine your ultimate fate!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Kirby's Block Ball-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19951214T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>HAL Laboratory</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<playcount>3</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20210402T204228</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tetris Rosy Retrospection.gb</path>
		<name>Tetris Rosy Retrospection</name>
		<playcount>3</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20210421T041641</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Trip World.gb</path>
		<name>Trip World</name>
		<desc>Trip World is a 1992 platform video game developed and published by Sunsoft for the Game Boy. It was released in Japan on November 27, 1992, and in Europe in 1993. The game's plot centers around the bunny-like being Yakopoo and his quest to retrieve the flower of peace so that peace will return to Yakopoo's disarranged world. The protagonist's trademark ability is to shapeshift into different forms.

In Trip World, you play as a strange creature called Yakopoo, who has to recover his tribe's stolen flower to prevent the villagers from fighting each other.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Trip World-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19930317T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sunsoft</developer>
		<publisher>SUNSOFT</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20210421T030112</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pokemon - Spaceworld Silver Version.gb</path>
		<name>Pokemon - Spaceworld Silver Version</name>
		<playcount>2</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20210810T030649</lastplayed>
	</game>
</gameList>
